<root>
  <item>
    <word>abandon</word>
    <defn>To give up or relinquish control of, to surrender or to give oneself over, or to yield to one's emotions.</defn>
    <defn>To desist in doing, practicing, following, holding, or adhering to; to turn away from; to permit to lapse; to renounce; to discontinue.</defn>
    <defn>To leave behind; to desert as in a ship or a position, typically in response to overwhelming odds or impending dangers; to forsake, in spite of a duty or responsibility.</defn>
    <defn>To subdue; to take control of.</defn>
    <defn>To cast out; to banish; to expel; to reject.</defn>
    <defn>To no longer exercise a right, title, or interest, especially with no interest of reclaiming it again; to yield; to relinquish.</defn>
    <defn>To surrender to the insurer (an insured item), so as to claim a total loss.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>absence</word>
    <defn>A state of being away or withdrawn from a place or from companionship; the period of being away.</defn>
    <defn>Failure to be present where one is expected, wanted, or needed; nonattendance; deficiency.</defn>
    <defn>Lack; deficiency; nonexistence.</defn>
    <defn>Inattention to things present; abstraction (of mind).</defn>
    <defn>Temporary loss or disruption of consciousness, with sudden onset and recovery, and common in epilepsy.</defn>
    <defn>Lack of contact between blades.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>account</word>
    <defn>A registry of pecuniary transactions; a written or printed statement of business dealings or debts and credits, and also of other things subjected to a reckoning or review.</defn>
    <defn>A sum of money deposited at a bank and subject to withdrawal.</defn>
    <defn>A statement in general of reasons, causes, grounds, etc., explanatory of some event; a reason of an action to be done.</defn>
    <defn>A reason, grounds, consideration, motive; a person's sake.</defn>
    <defn>A business relationship involving the exchange of money and credit.</defn>
    <defn>A record of events; recital of transactions; a relation or narrative; a report; a description.</defn>
    <defn>An estimate or estimation; valuation; judgment.</defn>
    <defn>Importance; worth; value; esteem; judgement.</defn>
    <defn>An authorization to use a service.</defn>
    <defn>A reckoning; computation; calculation; enumeration; a record of some reckoning.</defn>
    <defn>Profit; advantage.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>achieve</word>
    <defn>To succeed in something, now especially in academic performance.</defn>
    <defn>To carry out successfully; to accomplish.</defn>
    <defn>To conclude, finish, especially successfully.</defn>
    <defn>To obtain, or gain (a desired result, objective etc.), as the result of exertion; to succeed in gaining; to win.</defn>
    <defn>To conclude, to turn out.</defn>
    <defn>To obtain (a material thing).</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>acknowledge</word>
    <defn>To admit the knowledge of; to recognize as a fact or truth; to declare one's belief in</defn>
    <defn>To own or recognize in a particular quality, character or relationship; to admit the claims or authority of; to give recognition to.</defn>
    <defn>To be grateful of (e.g. a benefit or a favour)</defn>
    <defn>To report (the receipt of a message to its sender).</defn>
    <defn>To own as genuine or valid; to assent to (a legal instrument) to give it validity; to avow or admit in legal form.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>activity</word>
    <defn>The state or quality of being active; activeness.</defn>
    <defn>Something done as an action or a movement.</defn>
    <defn>Something done for pleasure or entertainment, especially one involving movement or an excursion.</defn>
    <defn>(grammar) The lexical aspect (aktionsart) of verbs or predicates that change over time and have no natural end point.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>adapt</word>
    <defn>To make suitable; to make to correspond; to fit or suit</defn>
    <defn>To fit by alteration; to modify or remodel for a different purpose; to adjust</defn>
    <defn>To make by altering or fitting something else; to produce by change of form or character</defn>
    <defn>To make oneself comfortable to a new thing.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>adjust</word>
    <defn>To modify.</defn>
    <defn>To improve or rectify.</defn>
    <defn>To settle an insurance claim.</defn>
    <defn>To change to fit circumstances.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>adjustment</word>
    <defn>The action of adjusting something</defn>
    <defn>The result of adjusting something; a small change; a minor correction; a modification or alteration</defn>
    <defn>The settling or balancing of a financial account</defn>
    <defn>The behavioural process of balancing conflicting needs, or needs against obstacles in the environment.</defn>
    <defn>The assessment, by an insurance company, of a claim; the settlement of such a claim</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>administration</word>
    <defn>The act of administering; government of public affairs; the service rendered, or duties assumed, in conducting affairs; the conducting of any office or employment; direction.</defn>
    <defn>A body that administers; the executive part of government; the persons collectively who are entrusted with the execution of laws and the superintendence of public affairs; the chief magistrate and his cabinet or council; or the council, or ministry, alone, as in Great Britain.</defn>
    <defn>The act of administering, or tendering something to another; dispensation.</defn>
    <defn>Management.</defn>
    <defn>An arrangement whereby an insolvent company can continue trading under supervision.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>administrator</word>
    <defn>One who administers affairs; one who directs, manages, executes, or dispenses, whether in civil, judicial, political, or ecclesiastical affairs; a manager</defn>
    <defn>A person who manages or settles the estate of an intestate, or of a testator when there is no competent executor; one to whom the right of administration has been committed by competent authority</defn>
    <defn>One who is responsible for software installation, management, information and maintenance of a computer or network</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>adolescent</word>
    <defn>A person who is in adolescence; someone who has reached puberty but is not yet an adult.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>advance</word>
    <defn>A forward move; improvement or progression.</defn>
    <defn>An addition to the price; rise in price or value.</defn>
    <defn>(in the plural) An opening approach or overture, especially of an unwelcome or sexual nature.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>advice</word>
    <defn>An opinion offered in an effort to be helpful.</defn>
    <defn>Deliberate consideration; knowledge.</defn>
    <defn>(commonly in plural) Information or news given; intelligence</defn>
    <defn>In language about financial transactions executed by formal documents, an advisory document.</defn>
    <defn>In commercial language, information communicated by letter; used chiefly in reference to drafts or bills of exchange</defn>
    <defn>A communication providing information, such as how an uncertain area of law might apply to possible future actions</defn>
    <defn>Counseling to perform a specific legal act.</defn>
    <defn>Counseling to perform a specific illegal act.</defn>
    <defn>In aspect-oriented programming, the code whose execution is triggered when a join point is reached.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>affair</word>
    <defn>(often in the plural) Something which is done or is to be done; business of any kind, commercial, professional, or public.</defn>
    <defn>Any proceeding or action which it is wished to refer to or characterize vaguely.</defn>
    <defn>An action or engagement not of sufficient magnitude to be called a battle.</defn>
    <defn>A material object (vaguely designated).</defn>
    <defn>A romantic relationship with someone who is not one's regular partner (boyfriend, girlfriend).</defn>
    <defn>A person with whom someone has an adulterous relationship.</defn>
    <defn>A party or social gathering, especially of a formal nature.</defn>
    <defn>The (male or female) genitals.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>afternoon</word>
    <defn>The part of the day from noon or lunchtime until sunset, evening, or suppertime or 6pm.</defn>
    <defn>The later part of anything, often with implications of decline.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>agency</word>
    <defn>The capacity, condition, or state of acting or of exerting power.</defn>
    <defn>The capacity of individuals to act independently and to make their own free choices.</defn>
    <defn>A medium through which power is exerted or an end is achieved.</defn>
    <defn>The office or function of an agent; also, the relationship between a principal and that person's agent.</defn>
    <defn>A department or other administrative unit of a government; also, the office or headquarters of, or the district administered by such unit of government.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>agreement</word>
    <defn>An understanding between entities to follow a specific course of conduct.</defn>
    <defn>A state whereby several parties share a view or opinion; the state of not contradicting one another.</defn>
    <defn>A legally binding contract enforceable in a court of law.</defn>
    <defn>(grammar) Rules that exist in many languages that force some parts of a sentence to be used or inflected differently depending on certain attributes of other parts.</defn>
    <defn>(chiefly in the plural) An agreeable quality.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>ahead</word>
    <defn>In or to the front; in advance; onward.</defn>
    <defn>In the direction one is facing or moving.</defn>
    <defn>In or for the future.</defn>
    <defn>At an earlier time.</defn>
    <defn>Having progressed more.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>all</word>
    <defn>(with a possessive pronoun) Everything that one is capable of.</defn>
    <defn>The totality of one's possessions.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>although</word>
    <defn>Though, even though, in spite of or despite the fact that: introducing a clause that expresses a concession.</defn>
    <defn>But, except.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>analysis</word>
    <defn>Decomposition into components in order to study (a complex thing, concept, theory etc.).</defn>
    <defn>The result of such a process.</defn>
    <defn>The mathematical study of functions, sequences, series, limits, derivatives and integrals.</defn>
    <defn>Proof by deduction from known truths.</defn>
    <defn>The process of breaking down a substance into its constituent parts, or the result of this process.</defn>
    <defn>The analytical study of melodies, harmonies, sequences, repetitions, variations, quotations, juxtapositions, and surprises.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>angle</word>
    <defn>A corner where two walls intersect.</defn>
    <defn>A change in direction.</defn>
    <defn>A viewpoint; a way of looking at something.</defn>
    <defn>The focus of a news story.</defn>
    <defn>Any of various hesperiid butterflies.</defn>
    <defn>A storyline between two wrestlers, providing the background for and approach to a feud.</defn>
    <defn>An ulterior motive; a scheme or means of benefitting from a situation, usually hidden, often immoral</defn>
    <defn>A projecting or sharp corner; an angular fragment.</defn>
    <defn>Any of the four cardinal points of an astrological chart: the Ascendant, the Midheaven, the Descendant and the Imum Coeli.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>anticipate</word>
    <defn>To act before (someone), especially to prevent an action.</defn>
    <defn>To take up or introduce (something) prematurely.</defn>
    <defn>To know of (something) before it happens; to expect.</defn>
    <defn>To eagerly wait for (something)</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>anxiety</word>
    <defn>An unpleasant state of mental uneasiness, nervousness, apprehension and obsession or concern about some uncertain event.</defn>
    <defn>An uneasy or distressing desire (for something).</defn>
    <defn>A state of restlessness and agitation, often accompanied by a distressing sense of oppression or tightness in the stomach.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>appear</word>
    <defn>To come or be in sight; to be in view; to become visible.</defn>
    <defn>To come before the public.</defn>
    <defn>To stand in presence of some authority, tribunal, or superior person, to answer a charge, plead a cause, etc.; to present oneself as a party or advocate before a court, or as a person to be tried.</defn>
    <defn>To become visible to the apprehension of the mind; to be known as a subject of observation or comprehension, or as a thing proved; to be obvious or manifest.</defn>
    <defn>To seem; to have a certain semblance; to look.</defn>
    <defn>To bring into view.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>approximately</word>
    <defn>Imprecise but close to in quantity or amount.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>arrest</word>
    <defn>The condition of being stopped, standstill.</defn>
    <defn>The judicial detention of a ship to secure a financial claim against its operators.</defn>
    <defn>Any seizure by power, physical or otherwise.</defn>
    <defn>A scurfiness of the back part of the hind leg of a horse.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>assistance</word>
    <defn>Aid; help; the act or result of assisting.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>assumption</word>
    <defn>The act of assuming, or taking to or upon oneself; the act of taking up or adopting.</defn>
    <defn>The act of taking for granted, or supposing a thing without proof; a supposition; an unwarrantable claim.</defn>
    <defn>The thing supposed; a postulate, or proposition assumed; a supposition.</defn>
    <defn>The minor or second proposition in a categorical syllogism.</defn>
    <defn>The taking of a person up into heaven.</defn>
    <defn>A festival in honor of the ascent of the Virgin Mary into heaven, celebrated on 15 August.</defn>
    <defn>Assumptio.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>at</word>
    <defn>To reply to or talk to someone, either online or face-to-face. (from the practice of targeting a message or reply to someone online by writing @name)</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>athletic</word>
    <defn>Having to do with athletes.</defn>
    <defn>Physically active.</defn>
    <defn>Having a muscular, well developed body, being in shape.</defn>
    <defn>An attribute of a motion or play which requires fine physical ability.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>attack</word>
    <defn>An attempt to cause damage, injury to, or death of opponent or enemy.</defn>
    <defn>An attempt to detract from the worth or credibility of, a person, position, idea, object, or thing, by physical, verbal, emotional, or other assault.</defn>
    <defn>(by extension) The beginning of active operations on anything.</defn>
    <defn>An attempt to exploit a vulnerability in a computer system.</defn>
    <defn>Collectively, the bowlers of a cricket side.</defn>
    <defn>Any contact with the ball other than a serve or block which sends the ball across the plane of the net.</defn>
    <defn>The sudden onset of a disease or condition.</defn>
    <defn>An active episode of a chronic or recurrent disease.</defn>
    <defn>The onset of a musical note, particularly with respect to the strength (and duration) of that onset.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>attend</word>
    <defn>To listen to (something or someone); to pay attention to; regard; heed.</defn>
    <defn>To listen (to, unto).</defn>
    <defn>To turn one's consideration (to); to deal with (a task, problem, concern etc.), to look after.</defn>
    <defn>To wait upon as a servant etc.; to accompany to assist (someone).</defn>
    <defn>To be present at (an event or place) in order to take part in some action or proceedings; to regularly go to (an event or place).</defn>
    <defn>To go to (a place) for some purpose (with at).</defn>
    <defn>To be present with; to accompany; to be united or consequent to.</defn>
    <defn>To wait for; to await; to remain, abide, or be in store for.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>auto</word>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>average</word>
    <defn>The arithmetic mean.</defn>
    <defn>Any measure of central tendency, especially any mean, the median, or the mode.</defn>
    <defn>(marine) Financial loss due to damage to transported goods; compensation for damage or loss.</defn>
    <defn>Customs duty or similar charge payable on transported goods.</defn>
    <defn>Proportional or equitable distribution of financial expense.</defn>
    <defn>An indication of a player's ability calculated from his scoring record, etc.</defn>
    <defn>(in the plural) In the corn trade, the medial price of the several kinds of grain in the principal corn markets.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>bar</word>
    <defn>A solid, more or less rigid object of metal or wood with a uniform cross-section smaller than its length.</defn>
    <defn>A solid metal object with uniform (round, square, hexagonal, octagonal or rectangular) cross-section; in the US its smallest dimension is 1/4 inch or greater, a piece of thinner material being called a strip.</defn>
    <defn>A cuboid piece of any solid commodity.</defn>
    <defn>A broad shaft, or band, or stripe.</defn>
    <defn>The sign indicating that the characteristic of a logarithm is negative, conventionally placed above the digit(s) to show that it applies to the characteristic only and not to the mantissa.</defn>
    <defn>A similar sign indicating that the charge on a particle is negative (and that consequently the particle is in fact an antiparticle).</defn>
    <defn>A business licensed to sell alcoholic drinks for consumption on the premises, or the premises themselves; public house.</defn>
    <defn>The counter of such premises.</defn>
    <defn>A counter, or simply a cabinet, from which alcoholic drinks are served in a private house or a hotel room.</defn>
    <defn>An establishment where alcohol and sometimes other refreshments are served.</defn>
    <defn>An informal establishment selling food to be consumed on the premises.</defn>
    <defn>An establishment offering cosmetic services.</defn>
    <defn>An official order or pronouncement that prohibits some activity.</defn>
    <defn>(Parliament) A dividing line (physical or notional) in the chamber of a legislature beyond which only members and officials may pass.</defn>
    <defn>The railing surrounding the part of a courtroom in which the judges, lawyers, defendants and witnesses stay</defn>
    <defn>A vertical line across a musical staff dividing written music into sections, typically of equal durational value.</defn>
    <defn>One of those musical sections.</defn>
    <defn>A horizontal pole that must be crossed in high jump and pole vault</defn>
    <defn>Any level of achievement regarded as a challenge to be overcome.</defn>
    <defn>The central divider between the inner and outer table of a backgammon board, where stones are placed if they are hit.</defn>
    <defn>An addition to a military medal, on account of a subsequent act</defn>
    <defn>A linear shoaling landform feature within a body of water.</defn>
    <defn>A ridge or succession of ridges of sand or other substance, especially a formation extending across the mouth of a river or harbor or off a beach, and which may obstruct navigation. (FM 55-501).</defn>
    <defn>One of the ordinaries in heraldry; a fess.</defn>
    <defn>A city gate, in some British place names.</defn>
    <defn>A drilling or tamping rod.</defn>
    <defn>A vein or dike crossing a lode.</defn>
    <defn>A gatehouse of a castle or fortified town.</defn>
    <defn>The part of the crust of a horse's hoof which is bent inwards towards the frog at the heel on each side, and extends into the centre of the sole.</defn>
    <defn>(in the plural) The space between the tusks and grinders in the upper jaw of a horse, in which the bit is placed.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>base</word>
    <defn>Something from which other things extend; a foundation.</defn>
    <defn>The starting point of a logical deduction or thought; basis.</defn>
    <defn>A permanent structure for housing military personnel and material.</defn>
    <defn>The place where decisions for an organization are made; headquarters.</defn>
    <defn>A basic but essential component or ingredient.</defn>
    <defn>A substance used as a mordant in dyeing.</defn>
    <defn>Foundation: a cosmetic cream to make the face appear uniform.</defn>
    <defn>Any of a class of generally water-soluble compounds, having bitter taste, that turn red litmus blue, and react with acids to form salts.</defn>
    <defn>Important areas in games and sports.</defn>
    <defn>The lowermost part of a column, between the shaft and the pedestal or pavement.</defn>
    <defn>The end of a leaf, petal or similar organ where it is attached to its support.</defn>
    <defn>The name of the controlling terminal of a bipolar transistor (BJT).</defn>
    <defn>The lowest side of a in a triangle or other polygon, or the lowest face of a cone, pyramid or other polyhedron laid flat.</defn>
    <defn>The lowest third of a shield or escutcheon.</defn>
    <defn>The lower part of the field. See escutcheon.</defn>
    <defn>A number raised to the power of an exponent.</defn>
    <defn>The set of sets from which a topology is generated.</defn>
    <defn>A topological space, looked at in relation to one of its covering spaces, fibrations, or bundles.</defn>
    <defn>A sequence of elements not jointly stabilized by any nontrivial group element.</defn>
    <defn>(acrobatics, cheerleading) In hand-to-hand balance, the person who supports the flyer; the person that remains in contact with the ground.</defn>
    <defn>A morpheme (or morphemes) that serves as a basic foundation on which affixes can be attached.</defn>
    <defn>The smallest kind of cannon.</defn>
    <defn>The housing of a horse.</defn>
    <defn>(in the plural) A kind of skirt (often of velvet or brocade, but sometimes of mailed armour) which hung from the middle to about the knees, or lower.</defn>
    <defn>The lower part of a robe or petticoat.</defn>
    <defn>An apron.</defn>
    <defn>A line in a survey which, being accurately determined in length and position, serves as the origin from which to compute the distances and positions of any points or objects connected with it by a system of triangles.</defn>
    <defn>A group of voters who almost always support a single party's candidates for elected office.</defn>
    <defn>The forces and relations of production that produce the necessities and amenities of life.</defn>
    <defn>A material that holds paint or other materials together; a binder.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>basically</word>
    <defn>In a fundamental, essential or basic manner</defn>
    <defn>Mostly; generally; for the most part</defn>
    <defn>(filler) used to refer to the most important or fundamental point the speaker is making; sometimes tending towards a meaningless filler word</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>bed</word>
    <defn>A piece of furniture, usually flat and soft, on which to rest or sleep.</defn>
    <defn>A place, or flat surface or layer, on which something else rests or is laid.</defn>
    <defn>(heading) A layer or surface.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>begin</word>
    <defn>Beginning; start.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>belief</word>
    <defn>Mental acceptance of a claim as true.</defn>
    <defn>Faith or trust in the reality of something; often based upon one's own reasoning, trust in a claim, desire of actuality, and/or evidence considered.</defn>
    <defn>Something believed.</defn>
    <defn>The quality or state of believing.</defn>
    <defn>Religious faith.</defn>
    <defn>(in the plural) One's religious or moral convictions.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>belt</word>
    <defn>A band worn around the waist to hold clothing to one's body (usually pants), hold weapons (such as a gun or sword), or serve as a decorative piece of clothing.</defn>
    <defn>A band that is used in a machine to help transfer motion or power.</defn>
    <defn>A collection of rocky-constituted bodies (such as asteroids) which orbit a star.</defn>
    <defn>One of certain girdles or zones on the surface of the planets Jupiter and Saturn, supposed to be of the nature of clouds.</defn>
    <defn>A powerful blow, often made with a fist or heavy object.</defn>
    <defn>A quick drink of liquor.</defn>
    <defn>(usually capitalized) A geographical region known for a particular product, feature or demographic (Corn Belt, Bible Belt, Black Belt, Green Belt).</defn>
    <defn>The part of the strike zone at the height of the batter's waist.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>bench</word>
    <defn>A long seat with or without a back, found for example in parks and schools.</defn>
    <defn>The people who decide on the verdict; the judiciary.</defn>
    <defn>The place where the judges sit.</defn>
    <defn>The dignity of holding an official seat.</defn>
    <defn>The place where players (substitutes) and coaches sit when not playing.</defn>
    <defn>The number of players on a team able to participate, expressed in terms of length.</defn>
    <defn>A horizontal padded surface, usually adjustable in height and inclination and often with attached weight rack, used for proper posture during exercise.</defn>
    <defn>A bracket used to mount land surveying equipment onto a stone or a wall.</defn>
    <defn>A flat ledge in the slope of an earthwork, work of masonry, or similar.</defn>
    <defn>A thin strip of relatively flat land bounded by steeper slopes above and below.</defn>
    <defn>A kitchen surface on which to prepare food, a counter.</defn>
    <defn>A bathroom surface which holds the washbasin, a vanity.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>between</word>
    <defn>A kind of needle, shorter than a sharp, with a small rounded eye, used for making fine stitches on heavy fabrics.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>birth</word>
    <defn>The process of childbearing; the beginning of life.</defn>
    <defn>A beginning or start; a point of origin.</defn>
    <defn>The circumstances of one's background, ancestry, or upbringing.</defn>
    <defn>That which is born.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>birthday</word>
    <defn>The anniversary of the day on which someone is born.</defn>
    <defn>The anniversary of the day on which something is created.</defn>
    <defn>The date on which someone is born or something is created, more commonly called birthdate or date of birth.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>blow</word>
    <defn>A strong wind.</defn>
    <defn>A chance to catch one&#8217;s breath.</defn>
    <defn>Cocaine.</defn>
    <defn>Cannabis.</defn>
    <defn>(US Chicago Regional) Heroin.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>board</word>
    <defn>A relatively long, wide and thin piece of any material, usually wood or similar, often for use in construction or furniture-making.</defn>
    <defn>Regular meals or the amount paid for them in a place of lodging.</defn>
    <defn>The side of a ship.</defn>
    <defn>The distance a sailing vessel runs between tacks when working to windward.</defn>
    <defn>The wall that surrounds an ice hockey rink, often in plural.</defn>
    <defn>A long, narrow table, like that used in a medieval dining hall.</defn>
    <defn>A level or stage having a particular layout.</defn>
    <defn>A container for holding pre-dealt cards that is used to allow multiple sets of players to play the same cards.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>body</word>
    <defn>Physical frame.</defn>
    <defn>Main section.</defn>
    <defn>Coherent group.</defn>
    <defn>Material entity.</defn>
    <defn>The shank of a type, or the depth of the shank (by which the size is indicated).</defn>
    <defn>A three-dimensional object, such as a cube or cone.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>bomb</word>
    <defn>An explosive device used or intended as a weapon.</defn>
    <defn>A failure; an unpopular commercial product.</defn>
    <defn>A large amount of money.</defn>
    <defn>(social) Something highly effective or attractive.</defn>
    <defn>A cyclone whose central pressure drops at an average rate of at least one millibar per hour for at least 24 hours.</defn>
    <defn>A heavy-walled container designed to permit chemical reactions under high pressure.</defn>
    <defn>A great booming noise; a hollow sound.</defn>
    <defn>A woman&#8217;s breast.</defn>
    <defn>A professional wrestling throw in which an opponent is lifted and then slammed back-first down to the mat.</defn>
    <defn>A recreational drug ground up, wrapped, and swallowed.</defn>
    <defn>An act of jumping into water while keeping one's arms and legs tucked into the body, as in a squatting position, to maximize splashing.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>book</word>
    <defn>A collection of sheets of paper bound together to hinge at one edge, containing printed or written material, pictures, etc.</defn>
    <defn>A major division of a long work.</defn>
    <defn>The script of a musical or opera.</defn>
    <defn>(usually in the plural) Records of the accounts of a business.</defn>
    <defn>(whist) Six tricks taken by one side.</defn>
    <defn>Four of a kind</defn>
    <defn>A document, held by the referee, of the incidents happened in the game.</defn>
    <defn>The twenty-sixth Lenormand card.</defn>
    <defn>Any source of instruction.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>boom</word>
    <defn>A low-pitched, resonant sound, such as of an explosion.</defn>
    <defn>A rapid expansion or increase.</defn>
    <defn>One of the calls of certain monkeys or birds.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>boot</word>
    <defn>A heavy shoe that covers part of the leg.</defn>
    <defn>A blow with the foot; a kick.</defn>
    <defn>A flexible cover of rubber or plastic, which may be preformed to a particular shape and used to protect a shaft, lever, switch, or opening from dust, dirt, moisture, etc.</defn>
    <defn>A parking enforcement device used to immobilize a car until it can be towed or a fine is paid; a wheel clamp.</defn>
    <defn>A place at the side of a coach, where attendants rode; also, a low outside place before and behind the body of the coach.</defn>
    <defn>A place for baggage at either end of an old-fashioned stagecoach.</defn>
    <defn>(police) A recently arrived recruit; a rookie.</defn>
    <defn>The luggage storage compartment of a sedan or saloon car.</defn>
    <defn>A hard plastic case for a long firearm, typically moulded to the shape of the gun and intended for use in a vehicle.</defn>
    <defn>A bobbled ball.</defn>
    <defn>The inflated flag leaf sheath of a wheat plant.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>bother</word>
    <defn>Fuss, ado.</defn>
    <defn>Trouble, inconvenience.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>breath</word>
    <defn>Air expelled from the lungs.</defn>
    <defn>A rest or pause.</defn>
    <defn>A small amount of something, such as wind, or common sense.</defn>
    <defn>Fragrance; exhalation; odor; perfume.</defn>
    <defn>Gentle exercise, causing a quicker respiration.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>brick</word>
    <defn>A hardened rectangular block of mud, clay etc., used for building.</defn>
    <defn>Such hardened mud, clay, etc. considered collectively, as a building material.</defn>
    <defn>A helpful and reliable person.</defn>
    <defn>A shot which misses, particularly one which bounces directly out of the basket because of a too-flat trajectory, as if the ball were a heavier object.</defn>
    <defn>An electronic device, especially a heavy box-shaped one, that has become non-functional or obsolete.</defn>
    <defn>A community card (usually the turn or the river) which does not improve a player's hand.</defn>
    <defn>One kilo of cocaine.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>bridge</word>
    <defn>A construction or natural feature that spans a divide.</defn>
    <defn>An arch or superstructure.</defn>
    <defn>A connection, real or abstract.</defn>
    <defn>Any of several electrical devices that measure characteristics such as impedance and inductance by balancing different parts of a circuit</defn>
    <defn>The situation where a lone rider or small group of riders closes the space between them and the rider or group in front.</defn>
    <defn>A solid crust of undissolved salt in a water softener.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>brother</word>
    <defn>Son of the same parents as another person.</defn>
    <defn>A male fellow member of a religious community, church, trades union etc.</defn>
    <defn>A form of address to a man.</defn>
    <defn>A black male.</defn>
    <defn>Somebody, usually male, connected by a common cause or situation.</defn>
    <defn>Someone who is a peer, whether male or female.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>bury</word>
    <defn>A burrow.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>but</word>
    <defn>The outer room of a small two-room cottage.</defn>
    <defn>A limit; a boundary.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>capability</word>
    <defn>The power or ability to generate an outcome</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>car</word>
    <defn>A wheeled vehicle that moves independently, with at least three wheels, powered mechanically, steered by a driver and mostly for personal transportation.</defn>
    <defn>A wheeled vehicle, drawn by a horse or other animal; a chariot.</defn>
    <defn>An unpowered unit in a railroad train.</defn>
    <defn>An individual vehicle, powered or unpowered, in a multiple unit.</defn>
    <defn>The part of an airship, such as a balloon or dirigible, which houses the passengers and control apparatus.</defn>
    <defn>A sliding fitting that runs along a track.</defn>
    <defn>A floating perforated box for living fish.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>category</word>
    <defn>A group, often named or numbered, to which items are assigned based on similarity or defined criteria.</defn>
    <defn>A collection of objects, together with a transitively closed collection of composable arrows between them, such that every object has an identity arrow, and such that arrow composition is associative.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>celebrate</word>
    <defn>To extol or honour in a solemn manner.</defn>
    <defn>To honour by rites, by ceremonies of joy and respect, or by refraining from ordinary business; to observe duly.</defn>
    <defn>To engage in joyful activity in appreciation of an event.</defn>
    <defn>To perform or participate in, as a sacrament or solemn rite; to perform with appropriate rites.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>center</word>
    <defn>The point in the interior of a circle that is equidistant from all points on the circumference.</defn>
    <defn>The point in the interior of a sphere that is equidistant from all points on the circumference.</defn>
    <defn>The middle portion of something; the part well away from the edges.</defn>
    <defn>The point on a line that is midway between the ends.</defn>
    <defn>The subgroup (respectively, subring), denoted Z(G), of those elements of a given group (respectively, ring) G that commute with every element of G.</defn>
    <defn>A place where the greater part of some function or activity occurs.</defn>
    <defn>A topic that is particularly important in a given context.</defn>
    <defn>A player in the middle of the playing area</defn>
    <defn>A player who can go all over the court, except the shooting circles.</defn>
    <defn>A pass played into the centre of the pitch.</defn>
    <defn>One of the backs operating in a central area of the pitch, either the inside centre or outside centre.</defn>
    <defn>A temporary structure upon which the materials of a vault or arch are supported in position until the work becomes self-supporting.</defn>
    <defn>One of the two conical steel pins in a lathe, etc., upon which the work is held, and about which it revolves.</defn>
    <defn>The ensemble of moderate or centrist political parties.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>chase</word>
    <defn>A hunt.</defn>
    <defn>A large country estate where game may be shot or hunted.</defn>
    <defn>A wild animal that is hunted.</defn>
    <defn>(real tennis) A division of the floor of a gallery, marked by a figure or otherwise; the spot where a ball falls, and between which and the dedans the adversary must drive the ball in order to gain a point.</defn>
    <defn>One or more riders who are ahead of the peloton and trying to join the race or stage leaders.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>cheap</word>
    <defn>Trade; traffic; chaffer; chaffering.</defn>
    <defn>A market; marketplace.</defn>
    <defn>Price.</defn>
    <defn>A low price; a bargain.</defn>
    <defn>Cheapness; lowness of price; abundance of supply.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>cheese</word>
    <defn>A dairy product made from curdled or cultured milk.</defn>
    <defn>That which is melodramatic, overly emotional, or clich&#233;, i.e. cheesy.</defn>
    <defn>Money.</defn>
    <defn>In skittles, the roughly ovoid object that is thrown to knock down the skittles.</defn>
    <defn>A fastball.</defn>
    <defn>Smegma.</defn>
    <defn>Holed pattern of circuitry to decrease pattern density.</defn>
    <defn>The flat, circular, mucilaginous fruit of the dwarf mallow (Malva rotundifolia) or marshmallow (Althaea officinalis).</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>chemical</word>
    <defn>An addictive drug.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>chief</word>
    <defn>A leader or head of a group of people, organisation, etc.</defn>
    <defn>The top part of a shield or escutcheon; more specifically, an ordinary consisting of the upper part of the field cut off by a horizontal line, generally occupying the top third.</defn>
    <defn>The principal part or top of anything.</defn>
    <defn>An informal term of address, sometimes ironic.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>church</word>
    <defn>A Christian house of worship; a building where Christian religious services take place.</defn>
    <defn>Christians collectively seen as a single spiritual community; Christianity.</defn>
    <defn>A local group of people who follow the same Christian religious beliefs, local or general.</defn>
    <defn>A particular denomination of Christianity.</defn>
    <defn>Organized religion in general or a specific religion considered as a political institution.</defn>
    <defn>Any religious group.</defn>
    <defn>Assembly.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>civil</word>
    <defn>Having to do with people and government office as opposed to the military or religion.</defn>
    <defn>Behaving in a reasonable or polite manner.</defn>
    <defn>Relating to private relations among citizens, as opposed to criminal matters.</defn>
    <defn>Secular.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>classic</word>
    <defn>A perfect and/or early example of a particular style.</defn>
    <defn>An artistic work of lasting worth, such as a film or song.</defn>
    <defn>The author of such a work.</defn>
    <defn>A major, long-standing sporting event</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>classroom</word>
    <defn>A room, often in a school, where classes take place</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>climate</word>
    <defn>An area of the earth's surface between two parallels of latitude.</defn>
    <defn>A region of the Earth.</defn>
    <defn>The long-term manifestations of weather and other atmospheric conditions in a given area or country, now usually represented by the statistical summary of its weather conditions during a period long enough to ensure that representative values are obtained (generally 30 years).</defn>
    <defn>The context in general of a particular political, moral etc. situation.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>close</word>
    <defn>An end or conclusion.</defn>
    <defn>The manner of shutting; the union of parts; junction.</defn>
    <defn>A grapple in wrestling.</defn>
    <defn>The conclusion of a strain of music; cadence.</defn>
    <defn>A double bar marking the end.</defn>
    <defn>(travel) The time when checkin staff will no longer accept passengers for a flight.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>coast</word>
    <defn>The edge of the land where it meets an ocean, sea, gulf, bay, or large lake.</defn>
    <defn>The side or edge of something.</defn>
    <defn>A region of land; a district or country.</defn>
    <defn>A region of the air or heavens.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>cold</word>
    <defn>(of a thing) Having a low temperature.</defn>
    <defn>Unfriendly, emotionally distant or unfeeling.</defn>
    <defn>Dispassionate, not prejudiced or partisan, impartial.</defn>
    <defn>Completely unprepared; without introduction.</defn>
    <defn>Unconscious or deeply asleep; deprived of the metaphorical heat associated with life or consciousness.</defn>
    <defn>(usually with "have" or "know" transitively) Perfectly, exactly, completely; by heart.</defn>
    <defn>(usually with "have" transitively) Cornered, done for.</defn>
    <defn>Not pungent or acrid.</defn>
    <defn>Unexciting; dull; uninteresting.</defn>
    <defn>Affecting the sense of smell (as of hunting dogs) only feebly; having lost its odour.</defn>
    <defn>Not sensitive; not acute.</defn>
    <defn>Distant; said, in the game of hunting for some object, of a seeker remote from the thing concealed. Compare warm and hot.</defn>
    <defn>Having a bluish effect; not warm in colour.</defn>
    <defn>Rarely used or accessed, and thus able to be relegated to slower storage.</defn>
    <defn>Without compassion; heartless; ruthless</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>college</word>
    <defn>A corporate group; a group of colleagues.</defn>
    <defn>(in some proper nouns) A group sharing common purposes or goals.</defn>
    <defn>An academic institution.</defn>
    <defn>A specialized division of a university.</defn>
    <defn>An institution of higher education teaching undergraduates.</defn>
    <defn>A university.</defn>
    <defn>Attendance at an institution of higher education.</defn>
    <defn>A postsecondary institution that offers vocational training and/or associate's degrees.</defn>
    <defn>A non-specialized, semi-autonomous division of a university, with its own faculty, departments, library, etc.</defn>
    <defn>An institution of further education at an intermediate level; sixth form.</defn>
    <defn>An institution for adult education at a basic or intermediate level (teaching those of any age).</defn>
    <defn>A high school or secondary school.</defn>
    <defn>A private (non-government) primary or high school.</defn>
    <defn>A residential hall associated with a university, possibly having its own tutors.</defn>
    <defn>(in Chile) A bilingual school.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>column</word>
    <defn>A solid upright structure designed usually to support a larger structure above it, such as a roof or horizontal beam, but sometimes for decoration.</defn>
    <defn>A vertical line of entries in a table, usually read from top to bottom.</defn>
    <defn>A body of troops or army vehicles, usually strung out along a road.</defn>
    <defn>A body of text meant to be read line by line, especially in printed material that has multiple adjacent such on a single page.</defn>
    <defn>(by extension) A recurring feature in a periodical, especially an opinion piece, especially by a single author or small rotating group of authors, or on a single theme.</defn>
    <defn>The gynostemium</defn>
    <defn>(chemistry) An object used to separate the different components of a liquid or to purify chemical compounds.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>comedy</word>
    <defn>A choric song of celebration or revel, especially in Ancient Greece.</defn>
    <defn>A light, amusing play with a happy ending.</defn>
    <defn>(Medieval Europe) A narrative poem with an agreeable ending (e.g., The Divine Comedy).</defn>
    <defn>A dramatic work that is light and humorous or satirical in tone.</defn>
    <defn>The genre of such works.</defn>
    <defn>Entertainment composed of jokes, satire, or humorous performance.</defn>
    <defn>A humorous event.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>committee</word>
    <defn>A body of one or more persons convened for the accomplishment of some specific purpose, typically with formal protocols.</defn>
    <defn>A guardian; someone in charge of another person deemed to be unable to look after himself or herself.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>communication</word>
    <defn>The act or fact of communicating anything; transmission.</defn>
    <defn>The concept or state of exchanging data or information between entities.</defn>
    <defn>An instance of information transfer; a conversation or discourse.</defn>
    <defn>A passageway or opening between two locations; connection.</defn>
    <defn>A connection between two tissues, organs, or cavities.</defn>
    <defn>Association; company.</defn>
    <defn>Participation in Holy Communion.</defn>
    <defn>A trope by which a speaker assumes that his hearer is a partner in his sentiments, and says "we" instead of "I" or "you".</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>community</word>
    <defn>A group sharing a common understanding, and often the same language, law, manners, and/or tradition.</defn>
    <defn>A residential or religious collective; a commune.</defn>
    <defn>A group of interdependent organisms inhabiting the same region and interacting with each other.</defn>
    <defn>The condition of having certain attitudes and interests in common.</defn>
    <defn>Common enjoyment or possession; participation.</defn>
    <defn>Common character; likeness.</defn>
    <defn>Commonness; frequency.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>compete</word>
    <defn>To be in battle or in a rivalry with another for the same thing, position, or reward; to contend</defn>
    <defn>To be in a position in which it is possible to win or triumph.</defn>
    <defn>To take part in a contest, game or similar event</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>complete</word>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>compose</word>
    <defn>To make something by merging parts.</defn>
    <defn>To make up the whole; to constitute.</defn>
    <defn>To comprise.</defn>
    <defn>To construct by mental labor; to think up; particularly, to produce or create a literary or musical work.</defn>
    <defn>(sometimes reflexive) To calm; to free from agitation.</defn>
    <defn>To arrange the elements of a photograph or other picture.</defn>
    <defn>To settle (an argument, dispute etc.); to come to a settlement.</defn>
    <defn>To arrange in proper form; to reduce to order; to put in proper state or condition.</defn>
    <defn>To arrange (types) in a composing stick for printing; to typeset.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>conclusion</word>
    <defn>The end, finish, close or last part of something.</defn>
    <defn>The outcome or result of a process or act.</defn>
    <defn>A decision reached after careful thought.</defn>
    <defn>In an argument or syllogism, the proposition that follows as a necessary consequence of the premises.</defn>
    <defn>The end or close of a pleading, e.g. the formal ending of an indictment, "against the peace", etc.</defn>
    <defn>An estoppel or bar by which a person is held to a particular position.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>concrete</word>
    <defn>A solid mass formed by the coalescence of separate particles; a compound substance, a concretion.</defn>
    <defn>Specifically, a building material created by mixing cement, water, and aggregate such as gravel and sand.</defn>
    <defn>Sugar boiled down from cane juice to a solid mass.</defn>
    <defn>A dessert of frozen custard with various toppings.</defn>
    <defn>An extract of herbal materials that has a semi-solid consistency, especially when such materials are partly aromatic.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>confirm</word>
    <defn>To strengthen; to make firm or resolute.</defn>
    <defn>To assure the accuracy of previous statements.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>considerable</word>
    <defn>A thing to be considered, consideration.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>constitutional</word>
    <defn>A walk that is taken regularly for good health and wellbeing.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>container</word>
    <defn>Someone who contains; something that contains.</defn>
    <defn>An item in which objects, materials or data can be stored or transported.</defn>
    <defn>A very large, typically metal, box used for transporting goods.</defn>
    <defn>(by extension) Someone who holds people in their seats or in a (reasonably) calm state.</defn>
    <defn>A file format that can hold various types of data.</defn>
    <defn>An abstract data type whose instances are collections of other objects.</defn>
    <defn>Any user interface component that can hold further (child) components.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>contest</word>
    <defn>Controversy; debate.</defn>
    <defn>Struggle for superiority; combat.</defn>
    <defn>A competition.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>controversy</word>
    <defn>A debate or discussion of opposing opinions; (generally) strife.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>convention</word>
    <defn>A meeting or gathering.</defn>
    <defn>A formal deliberative assembly of mandated delegates.</defn>
    <defn>The convening of a formal meeting.</defn>
    <defn>A formal agreement, contract or pact.</defn>
    <defn>A treaty or supplement to such.</defn>
    <defn>A practice or procedure widely observed in a group, especially to facilitate social interaction; a custom.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>cookie</word>
    <defn>A small, flat, baked good which is either crisp or soft but firm.</defn>
    <defn>A sweet baked good (as in the previous sense) usually having chocolate chips, fruit, nuts etc. baked into it.</defn>
    <defn>A bun.</defn>
    <defn>An attractive young woman.</defn>
    <defn>The female genitalia.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>cooperation</word>
    <defn>(usually uncountable) The act of cooperating.</defn>
    <defn>Active help from a person, organization, etc., such as an orderly sharing of space or resources.</defn>
    <defn>Association for mutual benefit, such as for purposes of production or purchase.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>cop</word>
    <defn>A spider.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>core</word>
    <defn>The central part of fruit, containing the kernels or seeds.</defn>
    <defn>The heart or inner part of a physical thing</defn>
    <defn>The center or inner part of a space or area</defn>
    <defn>The most important part of a thing; the essence.</defn>
    <defn>The portion of a mold that creates an internal cavity within a casting or that makes a hole in or through a casting.</defn>
    <defn>The bony process which forms the central axis of the horns in many animals.</defn>
    <defn>Magnetic data storage.</defn>
    <defn>The material between surface materials in a structured composite sandwich material.</defn>
    <defn>The inner part of a nuclear reactor in which the nuclear reaction takes place.</defn>
    <defn>A piece of ferromagnetic material (i.e. soft iron), inside the windings of an electromagnet, that channels the magnetic field.</defn>
    <defn>A disorder of sheep caused by worms in the liver.</defn>
    <defn>A tiny sample of organic material obtained by means of a fine-needle biopsy.</defn>
    <defn>The central part of a protein structure consisting in mostly hydrophobic aminoacids.</defn>
    <defn>The set of feasible allocations that cannot be improved upon by a subset (a coalition) of the economy's agents.</defn>
    <defn>A hollow cylindrical piece of cardboard around which a web of paper or plastic is winded.</defn>
    <defn>An atomic nucleus plus inner electrons (i.e. except valence electrons).</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>corner</word>
    <defn>The point where two converging lines meet; an angle, either external or internal.</defn>
    <defn>An edge or extremity; the part farthest from the center; hence, any quarter or part, or the direction in which it lies.</defn>
    <defn>A secret or secluded place; a remote or out of the way place; a nook.</defn>
    <defn>An embarrassing situation; a difficulty.</defn>
    <defn>(heading) Relating to the playing field.</defn>
    <defn>A place where people meet for a particular purpose.</defn>
    <defn>A point scored in a rubber at whist.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>corporate</word>
    <defn>A bond issued by a corporation.</defn>
    <defn>A short film produced for internal use in a business, e.g. for training, rather than for a general audience.</defn>
    <defn>A corporation that franchises, as opposed to than an individual franchise.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>council</word>
    <defn>Discussion or deliberation.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>counselor</word>
    <defn>A professional who counsels people, especially on personal problems.</defn>
    <defn>An attorney.</defn>
    <defn>A high ranking diplomat, usually just below an ambassador or minister.</defn>
    <defn>A children&#8217;s supervisor, usually at camp.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>count</word>
    <defn>A charge of misconduct brought in a legal proceeding.</defn>
    <defn>The number of balls and strikes, respectively, on a batter's in-progress plate appearance.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>country</word>
    <defn>(chiefly British) An area of land; a district, region.</defn>
    <defn>A set region of land having particular human occupation or agreed limits, especially inhabited by members of the same race, speakers of the same language etc., or associated with a given person, occupation, species etc.</defn>
    <defn>The territory of a nation, especially an independent nation state or formerly independent nation; a political entity asserting ultimate authority over a geographical area; a sovereign state.</defn>
    <defn>The rock through which a vein runs.</defn>
    <defn>The female genitalia, especially the vagina.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>crack</word>
    <defn>A thin and usually jagged space opened in a previously solid material.</defn>
    <defn>A narrow opening.</defn>
    <defn>The sharp sound made when solid material breaks.</defn>
    <defn>Any sharp sound.</defn>
    <defn>A sharp, resounding blow.</defn>
    <defn>An attempt at something.</defn>
    <defn>Vagina.</defn>
    <defn>The space between the buttocks.</defn>
    <defn>Conviviality; fun; good conversation, chat, gossip, or humorous storytelling; good company.</defn>
    <defn>Business; events; news.</defn>
    <defn>A program or procedure designed to circumvent restrictions or usage limits on software.</defn>
    <defn>(elsewhere throughout the North of the UK) a meaningful chat.</defn>
    <defn>Extremely silly, absurd or off-the-wall ideas or prose.</defn>
    <defn>The tone of voice when changed at puberty.</defn>
    <defn>A mental flaw; a touch of craziness; partial insanity.</defn>
    <defn>A boast; boasting.</defn>
    <defn>Breach of chastity.</defn>
    <defn>A boy, generally a pert, lively boy.</defn>
    <defn>A brief time; an instant; a jiffy.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>crash</word>
    <defn>A sudden, intense, loud sound, as made for example by cymbals.</defn>
    <defn>An automobile, airplane, or other vehicle accident.</defn>
    <defn>A malfunction of computer software or hardware which causes it to shut down or become partially or totally inoperable.</defn>
    <defn>A sudden large decline of business or the prices of stocks (especially one that causes additional failures).</defn>
    <defn>A comedown from a drug.</defn>
    <defn>(collective) A group of rhinoceroses.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>creature</word>
    <defn>A living being; an animal or (sometimes derogatory) a human.</defn>
    <defn>A created thing, whether animate or inanimate; a creation.</defn>
    <defn>A being subservient to or dependent upon another.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>critical</word>
    <defn>In breakdancing, a kind of airflare move in which the dancer hops from one hand to the other.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>custom</word>
    <defn>Frequent repetition of the same behavior; way of behavior common to many; ordinary manner; habitual practice; method of doing, living or behaving.</defn>
    <defn>Traditional beliefs or rituals</defn>
    <defn>Habitual buying of goods; practice of frequenting, as a shop, factory, etc., for making purchases or giving orders; business support.</defn>
    <defn>Long-established practice, considered as unwritten law, and resting for authority on long consent; usage. See Usage, and Prescription.</defn>
    <defn>Familiar acquaintance; familiarity.</defn>
    <defn>Toll, tax, or tribute.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>customer</word>
    <defn>A patron, a client; one who purchases or receives a product or service from a business or merchant, or intends to do so.</defn>
    <defn>A person, especially one engaging in some sort of interaction with others.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>dad</word>
    <defn>A father, a male parent.</defn>
    <defn>(familiar) Used to address one's father</defn>
    <defn>Used to address an older adult male</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>damage</word>
    <defn>Injury or harm; the condition or measure of something not being intact.</defn>
    <defn>Cost or expense.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>darkness</word>
    <defn>The state of being dark; lack of light.</defn>
    <defn>Gloom.</defn>
    <defn>The product of being dark.</defn>
    <defn>The state or quality of reflecting little light, of tending to a blackish or brownish color.</defn>
    <defn>Evilness, lack of understanding or compassion, reference to death or suffering.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>dear</word>
    <defn>A very kind, loving person.</defn>
    <defn>A beloved person.</defn>
    <defn>An affectionate, familiar term of address, such as used between husband and wife.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>deficit</word>
    <defn>Deficiency in amount or quality; a falling short; lack.</defn>
    <defn>A situation wherein, or amount whereby, spending exceeds government revenue.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>demonstrate</word>
    <defn>To show how to use (something).</defn>
    <defn>To show the steps taken to create a logical argument or equation.</defn>
    <defn>To participate in or organize a demonstration.</defn>
    <defn>To show, display, or present; to prove or make evident</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>deny</word>
    <defn>To disallow or reject.</defn>
    <defn>To assert that something is not true.</defn>
    <defn>(ditransitive) To refuse to give or grant something to someone.</defn>
    <defn>To take something away from someone; to deprive of.</defn>
    <defn>To prevent from scoring.</defn>
    <defn>To disclaim connection with, responsibility for, etc.; to refuse to acknowledge; to disown; to abjure; to disavow.</defn>
    <defn>To refuse (to do or accept something).</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>department</word>
    <defn>A part, portion, or subdivision.</defn>
    <defn>A distinct course of life, action, study, or the like.</defn>
    <defn>A subdivision of an organization.</defn>
    <defn>A military subdivision of a country</defn>
    <defn>Act of departing; departure.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>develop</word>
    <defn>To change with a specific direction, progress.</defn>
    <defn>To progress through a sequence of stages.</defn>
    <defn>To advance; to further; to promote the growth of.</defn>
    <defn>To create.</defn>
    <defn>To bring out images latent in photographic film.</defn>
    <defn>To acquire something usually over a period of time.</defn>
    <defn>To place one's pieces actively.</defn>
    <defn>To cause a ball to become more open and available to be played on later. Usually by moving it away from the cushion, or by opening a pack.</defn>
    <defn>To change the form of (an algebraic expression, etc.) by executing certain indicated operations without changing the value.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>developing</word>
    <defn>To change with a specific direction, progress.</defn>
    <defn>To progress through a sequence of stages.</defn>
    <defn>To advance; to further; to promote the growth of.</defn>
    <defn>To create.</defn>
    <defn>To bring out images latent in photographic film.</defn>
    <defn>To acquire something usually over a period of time.</defn>
    <defn>To place one's pieces actively.</defn>
    <defn>To cause a ball to become more open and available to be played on later. Usually by moving it away from the cushion, or by opening a pack.</defn>
    <defn>To change the form of (an algebraic expression, etc.) by executing certain indicated operations without changing the value.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>differently</word>
    <defn>(manner) In a different way.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>dining</word>
    <defn>To eat; to eat dinner or supper.</defn>
    <defn>To give a dinner to; to furnish with the chief meal; to feed.</defn>
    <defn>To dine upon; to have to eat.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>direction</word>
    <defn>A theoretical line (physically or mentally) followed from a point of origin or towards a destination. May be relative (e.g. up, left, outbound, dorsal), geographical (e.g. north), rotational (e.g. clockwise), or with respect to an object or location (e.g. toward Boston).</defn>
    <defn>A general trend for future action.</defn>
    <defn>Guidance, instruction.</defn>
    <defn>The work of the director in cinema or theater; the skill of directing a film, play etc.</defn>
    <defn>The body of persons who guide or manage a matter; the directorate.</defn>
    <defn>A person's address.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>directly</word>
    <defn>In a direct manner; in a straight line or course.</defn>
    <defn>In a straightforward way; without anything intervening; not by secondary, but by direct means.</defn>
    <defn>Plainly, without circumlocution or ambiguity; absolutely; in express terms.</defn>
    <defn>Exactly; just.</defn>
    <defn>Straightforwardly; honestly.</defn>
    <defn>Immediately.</defn>
    <defn>Soon; next; when it becomes convenient.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>director</word>
    <defn>A counselor, confessor, or spiritual guide.</defn>
    <defn>That which directs or orientates something.</defn>
    <defn>A device that displays graphical information concerning the targets of a weapons system in real time.</defn>
    <defn>The common axis of symmetry of the molecules of a liquid crystal.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>disagree</word>
    <defn>To fail to agree; to have a different opinion or belief.</defn>
    <defn>To fail to conform or correspond with.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>discrimination</word>
    <defn>Discernment, the act of discriminating, discerning, distinguishing, noting or perceiving differences between things, with intent to understand rightly and make correct decisions.</defn>
    <defn>The act of recognizing the 'good' and 'bad' in situations and choosing good.</defn>
    <defn>That which discriminates; mark of distinction, a characteristic.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>dismiss</word>
    <defn>To discharge; to end the employment or service of.</defn>
    <defn>To order to leave.</defn>
    <defn>To dispel; to rid one&#8217;s mind of.</defn>
    <defn>To reject; to refuse to accept.</defn>
    <defn>To send or put away, to discard with disregard, contempt or disdain. (sometimes followed by as).</defn>
    <defn>To get a batsman out.</defn>
    <defn>To give someone a red card; to send off.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>dispute</word>
    <defn>An argument or disagreement, a failure to agree.</defn>
    <defn>Verbal controversy or disagreement; altercation; debate.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>diverse</word>
    <defn>Consisting of many different elements; various.</defn>
    <defn>Different; dissimilar; distinct; not the same</defn>
    <defn>Capable of various forms; multiform.</defn>
    <defn>Composed of people with a variety of different demographic characteristics in terms of, for example, ethnicity, gender, sexual orientation, socioeconomic status, etc., and having a sizeable representation of people that are minorities in a given area.</defn>
    <defn>Belonging to a minority group.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>drag</word>
    <defn>Resistance of the air (or some other fluid) to something moving through it.</defn>
    <defn>(foundry) The bottom part of a sand casting mold.</defn>
    <defn>A puff on a cigarette or joint.</defn>
    <defn>Someone or something that is annoying or frustrating, or disappointing; an obstacle to progress or enjoyment.</defn>
    <defn>A long open horse-drawn carriage with transverse or side seats.</defn>
    <defn>A large amount of backspin on the cue ball, causing the cue ball to slow down.</defn>
    <defn>A heavy harrow for breaking up ground.</defn>
    <defn>A kind of sledge for conveying heavy objects; also, a kind of low car or handcart.</defn>
    <defn>The bottom part of a flask or mould, the upper part being the cope.</defn>
    <defn>A steel instrument for completing the dressing of soft stone.</defn>
    <defn>The difference between the speed of a screw steamer under sail and that of the screw when the ship outruns the screw; or between the propulsive effects of the different floats of a paddle wheel.</defn>
    <defn>A skid or shoe for retarding the motion of a carriage wheel.</defn>
    <defn>Motion affected with slowness and difficulty, as if clogged.</defn>
    <defn>Witch house music.</defn>
    <defn>The last position in a line of hikers.</defn>
    <defn>(aerodynamics) The act of suppressing wind flow to slow an aircraft in flight, as by use of flaps when landing.</defn>
    <defn>A push somewhat under the centre of the cue ball, causing it to follow the object ball a short way.</defn>
    <defn>A device for guiding wood to the saw.</defn>
    <defn>A mailcoach.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>dramatic</word>
    <defn>Of or relating to the drama.</defn>
    <defn>Striking in appearance or effect.</defn>
    <defn>Having a powerful, expressive singing voice.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>dry</word>
    <defn>The process by which something is dried.</defn>
    <defn>A prohibitionist (of alcoholic beverages).</defn>
    <defn>An area of waterless country.</defn>
    <defn>(UK politics) A radical or hard-line Conservative; especially, one who supported the policies of British Prime Minister Margaret Thatcher in the 1980s.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>dust</word>
    <defn>Fine particles</defn>
    <defn>The earth, as the resting place of the dead.</defn>
    <defn>The earthy remains of bodies once alive; the remains of the human body.</defn>
    <defn>Something worthless.</defn>
    <defn>A low or mean condition.</defn>
    <defn>A disturbance or uproar.</defn>
    <defn>A totally disconnected set of points with a fractal structure.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>earth</word>
    <defn>The third planet of the Solar System; the world upon which humans live.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>eat</word>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>effect</word>
    <defn>The result or outcome of a cause.</defn>
    <defn>Impression left on the mind; sensation produced.</defn>
    <defn>Execution; performance; realization; operation.</defn>
    <defn>(sound engineering) An alteration, or device for producing an alteration, in sound after it has been produced by an instrument.</defn>
    <defn>(etc.) A scientific phenomenon, usually named after its discoverer.</defn>
    <defn>Consequence intended; purpose; meaning; general intent; with to.</defn>
    <defn>Reality; actual meaning; fact, as distinguished from mere appearance.</defn>
    <defn>Manifestation; expression; sign.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>effective</word>
    <defn>A soldier fit for duty</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>elderly</word>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>electronic</word>
    <defn>: Of or pertaining to an electron or electrons.</defn>
    <defn>Operating on the physical behavior of electrons, especially in semiconductors.</defn>
    <defn>Of or pertaining to the Internet.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>elementary</word>
    <defn>(mysticism) A supernatural being which is associated with the elements.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>empty</word>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>entrance</word>
    <defn>The action of entering, or going in.</defn>
    <defn>The act of taking possession, as of property, or of office.</defn>
    <defn>The place of entering, as a gate or doorway.</defn>
    <defn>The right to go in.</defn>
    <defn>The entering upon; the beginning, or that with which the beginning is made; the commencement; initiation.</defn>
    <defn>The causing to be entered upon a register, as a ship or goods, at a customhouse; an entering.</defn>
    <defn>The angle which the bow of a vessel makes with the water at the water line.</defn>
    <defn>The bow, or entire wedgelike forepart of a vessel, below the water line.</defn>
    <defn>When a musician starts playing or singing, entry.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>era</word>
    <defn>A unit of time, smaller than eons and greater than periods.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>essential</word>
    <defn>A necessary ingredient.</defn>
    <defn>A fundamental ingredient.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>establish</word>
    <defn>To make stable or firm; to confirm.</defn>
    <defn>To form; to found; to institute; to set up in business.</defn>
    <defn>To appoint or adopt, as officers, laws, regulations, guidelines, etc.; to enact; to ordain.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>evaluate</word>
    <defn>To draw conclusions from examining; to assess.</defn>
    <defn>To compute or determine the value of (an expression).</defn>
    <defn>To return or have a specific value.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>evening</word>
    <defn>The time of the day between dusk and night, when it gets dark.</defn>
    <defn>The time of the day between the approximate time of midwinter dusk and midnight (compare afternoon); the period after the end of regular office working hours.</defn>
    <defn>A concluding time period; a point in time near the end of something; the beginning of the end of something.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>everybody</word>
    <defn>All people.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>everyday</word>
    <defn>(rare) the ordinary or routine day or occasion</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>everyone</word>
    <defn>Every person.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>everywhere</word>
    <defn>In or to all locations under discussion.</defn>
    <defn>In or to a few or more locations.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>excellent</word>
    <defn>Having excelled, having surpassed.</defn>
    <defn>Of higher or the highest quality; splendid.</defn>
    <defn>Exceptionally good of its kind.</defn>
    <defn>Superior in kind or degree, irrespective of moral quality.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>exciting</word>
    <defn>To stir the emotions of.</defn>
    <defn>To arouse or bring out (e.g. feelings); to stimulate.</defn>
    <defn>To cause an electron to move to a higher than normal state; to promote an electron to an outer level.</defn>
    <defn>To energize (an electromagnet); to produce a magnetic field in.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>exhibit</word>
    <defn>An article formally introduced as evidence in a court.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>expense</word>
    <defn>A spending or consuming, often a disbursement of funds.</defn>
    <defn>The elimination or consumption of something, sometimes with the notion of loss or damage to the thing eliminated.</defn>
    <defn>Loss.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>explosion</word>
    <defn>A violent release of energy (sometimes mechanical, nuclear, or chemical.)</defn>
    <defn>A bursting due to pressure.</defn>
    <defn>A sudden uncontrolled increase.</defn>
    <defn>A sudden outburst.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>extension</word>
    <defn>The act of extending; a stretching out; enlargement in length or breadth; an increase</defn>
    <defn>The state of being extended</defn>
    <defn>A part of a building that has been extended from the original</defn>
    <defn>Capacity of a concept or general term to include a greater or smaller number of objects; &#8212; correlative of intension.</defn>
    <defn>A written engagement on the part of a creditor, allowing a debtor further time to pay a debt.</defn>
    <defn>The operation of stretching a broken bone so as to bring the fragments into the same straight line.</defn>
    <defn>An exercise in which an arm or leg is straightened against resistance.</defn>
    <defn>A simple offensive action, consisting of extending the weapon arm forward.</defn>
    <defn>A numerical code used to specify a specific telephone in a telecommunication network.</defn>
    <defn>An optional software component that adds functionality to an application.</defn>
    <defn>The set of tuples of values that, used as arguments, satisfy the predicate.</defn>
    <defn>(grammar) A kind of derivative morpheme applied to verbs in Bantu languages.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>extreme</word>
    <defn>The greatest or utmost point, degree or condition.</defn>
    <defn>Each of the things at opposite ends of a range or scale.</defn>
    <defn>A drastic expedient.</defn>
    <defn>Either of the two numbers at the ends of a proportion, as 1 and 6 in 1:2=3:6.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>fabric</word>
    <defn>An edifice or building.</defn>
    <defn>The structure of anything, the manner in which the parts of a thing are united; workmanship, texture, make.</defn>
    <defn>The framework underlying a structure.</defn>
    <defn>A material made of fibers, a textile or cloth.</defn>
    <defn>The appearance of crystalline grains in a rock.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>fade</word>
    <defn>A golf shot that (for the right-handed player) curves intentionally to the right. See slice, hook, draw.</defn>
    <defn>A fight.</defn>
    <defn>A gradual decrease in the brightness of a shot or the volume of sound or music (as a means of cutting to a new scene or starting a new song).</defn>
    <defn>The act of disappearing from a place so as not to be found; covert departure.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>faith</word>
    <defn>A trust or confidence in the intentions or abilities of a person, object, or ideal from prior empirical evidence.</defn>
    <defn>The process of forming or understanding abstractions, ideas, or beliefs, without empirical evidence, experience or observation.</defn>
    <defn>A religious or spiritual belief system.</defn>
    <defn>An obligation of loyalty or fidelity and the observance of such an obligation.</defn>
    <defn>Credibility or truth.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>fan</word>
    <defn>A hand-held device consisting of concertinaed material, or slats of material, gathered together at one end, that may be opened out into the shape of a sector of a circle and waved back and forth in order to move air towards oneself and cool oneself.</defn>
    <defn>An electrical or mechanical device for moving air, used for cooling people, machinery, etc.</defn>
    <defn>An instrument for winnowing grain, by moving which the grain is tossed and agitated, and the chaff is separated and blown away.</defn>
    <defn>A small vane or sail, used to keep the large sails of a smock mill always in the direction of the wind.</defn>
    <defn>A section of a tree having a finite number of branches</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>favorite</word>
    <defn>A person or thing who enjoys special regard or favour.</defn>
    <defn>A person who is preferred or trusted above all others.</defn>
    <defn>A contestant or competitor thought most likely to win.</defn>
    <defn>A bookmark in a web browser.</defn>
    <defn>(in the plural) A short curl dangling over the temples, fashionable in the reign of Charles II.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>fellow</word>
    <defn>A colleague or partner.</defn>
    <defn>A companion; a comrade.</defn>
    <defn>A man without good breeding or worth; an ignoble or mean man.</defn>
    <defn>An equal in power, rank, character, etc.</defn>
    <defn>One of a pair, or of two things used together or suited to each other; a mate.</defn>
    <defn>A person with common characteristics, being of the same kind, or in the same group.</defn>
    <defn>A male person; a man.</defn>
    <defn>A person; an individual, male or female.</defn>
    <defn>A rank or title in the professional world, usually given as "Fellow".</defn>
    <defn>(Aboriginal English) Used as a general intensifier</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>fiber</word>
    <defn>A material whose length is at least 1000 times its width.</defn>
    <defn>Moral strength and resolve.</defn>
    <defn>The preimage of a given point in the range of a map.</defn>
    <defn>Said to be of a morphism over a global element: The pullback of the said morphism along the said global element.</defn>
    <defn>A kind of lightweight thread of execution.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>file</word>
    <defn>A collection of papers collated and archived together.</defn>
    <defn>A roll or list.</defn>
    <defn>Course of thought; thread of narration.</defn>
    <defn>An aggregation of data on a storage device, identified by a name.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>finding</word>
    <defn>To encounter or discover by accident; to happen upon.</defn>
    <defn>To encounter or discover something being searched for; to locate.</defn>
    <defn>(ditransitive) To discover by study or experiment direct to an object or end.</defn>
    <defn>To gain, as the object of desire or effort.</defn>
    <defn>To attain to; to arrive at; to acquire.</defn>
    <defn>To point out.</defn>
    <defn>(ditransitive) To decide that, to discover that, to form the opinion that.</defn>
    <defn>To arrive at, as a conclusion; to determine as true; to establish.</defn>
    <defn>To supply; to furnish.</defn>
    <defn>To provide for</defn>
    <defn>To determine or judge.</defn>
    <defn>To discover game.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>fine</word>
    <defn>Fine champagne; French brandy.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>flow</word>
    <defn>A movement in people or things with a particular way in large numbers or amounts</defn>
    <defn>The movement of a real or figurative fluid.</defn>
    <defn>A formalization of the idea of the motion of particles in a fluid, as a group action of the real numbers on a set.</defn>
    <defn>The rising movement of the tide.</defn>
    <defn>Smoothness or continuity.</defn>
    <defn>The amount of a fluid that moves or the rate of fluid movement.</defn>
    <defn>A mental state characterized by concentration, focus and enjoyment of a given task.</defn>
    <defn>The emission of blood during menstruation.</defn>
    <defn>The ability to skilfully rap along to a beat.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>folk</word>
    <defn>A grouping of smaller peoples or tribes as a nation.</defn>
    <defn>The inhabitants of a region, especially the native inhabitants.</defn>
    <defn>Folk music.</defn>
    <defn>People in general.</defn>
    <defn>A particular group of people.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>forever</word>
    <defn>An extremely long time.</defn>
    <defn>A mythical time in the infinite future that will never come.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>formula</word>
    <defn>Any mathematical rule expressed symbolically.</defn>
    <defn>A symbolic expression of the structure of a compound.</defn>
    <defn>A plan or method for dealing with a problem or for achieving a result.</defn>
    <defn>A formal statement of doctrine, as in religion.</defn>
    <defn>A syntactic expression of a proposition, built up from quantifiers, logical connectives, variables, relation and operation symbols, and, depending on the type of logic, possibly other operators such as modal, temporal, deontic or epistemic ones.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>fortune</word>
    <defn>Destiny, especially favorable.</defn>
    <defn>The arrival of something in a sudden or unexpected manner; chance; accident.</defn>
    <defn>Good luck.</defn>
    <defn>One's wealth; the amount of money one has; especially, if it is vast.</defn>
    <defn>A large amount of money.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>fuel</word>
    <defn>Substance consumed to provide energy through combustion, or through chemical or nuclear reaction.</defn>
    <defn>Substance that provides nourishment for a living organism; food.</defn>
    <defn>Something that stimulates, encourages or maintains an action.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>fund</word>
    <defn>A sum or source of money.</defn>
    <defn>An organization managing such money.</defn>
    <defn>A large supply of something to be drawn upon.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>general</word>
    <defn>A great strategist or tactician.</defn>
    <defn>The head of certain religious orders, especially Dominicans or Jesuits.</defn>
    <defn>A commander of naval forces; an admiral.</defn>
    <defn>General anesthesia.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>girl</word>
    <defn>A female child, adolescent, or a young woman.</defn>
    <defn>A young female animal.</defn>
    <defn>(sometimes offensive) A woman, especially a young woman</defn>
    <defn>A female servant; a maid. (see usage notes)</defn>
    <defn>A queen (the playing card.)</defn>
    <defn>A term of endearment. (see usage notes)</defn>
    <defn>One's daughter.</defn>
    <defn>A roebuck two years old.</defn>
    <defn>Cocaine, especially in powder form.</defn>
    <defn>(somewhat childish) A female (tree, gene, etc).</defn>
    <defn>A boy or man who is weak or sentimental.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>given</word>
    <defn>(ditransitive) To move, shift, provide something abstract or concrete to someone or something or somewhere.</defn>
    <defn>(ditransitive) To estimate or predict (a duration or probability) for (something).</defn>
    <defn>To yield slightly when a force is applied.</defn>
    <defn>To collapse under pressure or force.</defn>
    <defn>To provide, as, a service or a broadcast.</defn>
    <defn>To lead (onto or into).</defn>
    <defn>To provide a view of.</defn>
    <defn>To exhibit as a product or result; to produce; to yield.</defn>
    <defn>To cause; to make; used with the infinitive.</defn>
    <defn>To cause (someone) to have; produce in (someone); effectuate.</defn>
    <defn>To allow or admit by way of supposition; to concede.</defn>
    <defn>To attribute; to assign; to adjudge.</defn>
    <defn>To communicate or announce (advice, tidings, etc.); to pronounce or utter (an opinion, a judgment, a shout, etc.).</defn>
    <defn>To grant power or permission to; to allow.</defn>
    <defn>To devote or apply (oneself).</defn>
    <defn>To become soft or moist.</defn>
    <defn>To shed tears; to weep.</defn>
    <defn>To have a misgiving.</defn>
    <defn>To be going on, to be occurring</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>glance</word>
    <defn>A brief or cursory look.</defn>
    <defn>A deflection.</defn>
    <defn>A stroke in which the ball is deflected to one side.</defn>
    <defn>A sudden flash of light or splendour.</defn>
    <defn>An incidental or passing thought or allusion.</defn>
    <defn>Any of various sulphides, mostly dark-coloured, which have a brilliant metallic lustre.</defn>
    <defn>Glance coal.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>global</word>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>go</word>
    <defn>A turn at something, or in something (e.g. a game).</defn>
    <defn>An attempt, a try.</defn>
    <defn>An approval or permission to do something, or that which has been approved.</defn>
    <defn>An act; the working or operation.</defn>
    <defn>A circumstance or occurrence; an incident, often unexpected.</defn>
    <defn>The fashion or mode.</defn>
    <defn>Noisy merriment.</defn>
    <defn>A glass of spirits; a quantity of spirits.</defn>
    <defn>The situation where a player cannot play a card which will not carry the aggregate count above thirty-one.</defn>
    <defn>A period of activity.</defn>
    <defn>(British slang) A dandy; a fashionable person.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>graduate</word>
    <defn>A person who is recognized by a university as having completed the requirements of a degree studied at the institution.</defn>
    <defn>A person who is recognized by a high school as having completed the requirements of a course of study at the school.</defn>
    <defn>A person who is recognized as having completed any level of education.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>grass</word>
    <defn>Any plant of the family Poaceae, characterized by leaves that arise from nodes in the stem and leaf bases that wrap around the stem, especially those grown as ground cover rather than for grain.</defn>
    <defn>A lawn.</defn>
    <defn>Marijuana.</defn>
    <defn>An informer, police informer; one who betrays a group (of criminals, etc) to the authorities.</defn>
    <defn>Sharp, closely spaced discontinuities in the trace of a cathode-ray tube, produced by random interference.</defn>
    <defn>Noise on an A-scope or similar type of radar display.</defn>
    <defn>That which is transitory.</defn>
    <defn>The surface of a mine.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>grave</word>
    <defn>An excavation in the earth as a place of burial</defn>
    <defn>Any place of interment; a tomb; a sepulcher.</defn>
    <defn>(by extension) Death, destruction.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>great</word>
    <defn>A person of major significance, accomplishment or acclaim.</defn>
    <defn>The main division in a pipe organ, usually the loudest division.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>greatest</word>
    <defn>Relatively large in scale, size, extent, number (i.e. having many parts or members) or duration (i.e. relatively long); very big.</defn>
    <defn>Of larger size or more importance than others of its kind.</defn>
    <defn>(qualifying nouns of family relationship) Involving more generations than the qualified word implies &#8212; as many extra generations as repetitions of the word great (from 1510s). [see Derived terms]</defn>
    <defn>(followed by 'with') Pregnant; large with young; full of.</defn>
    <defn>(except with 'friend' and similar words such as 'mate','buddy') Intimate; familiar.</defn>
    <defn>Extreme or more than usual.</defn>
    <defn>Of significant importance or consequence; important.</defn>
    <defn>(applied to actions, thoughts and feelings) Arising from or possessing idealism; admirable; superior; commanding; heroic; illustrious; eminent.</defn>
    <defn>Impressive or striking.</defn>
    <defn>Much in use; favoured.</defn>
    <defn>(applied to persons) Endowed with extraordinary powers; of exceptional talents or achievements; uncommonly gifted; able to accomplish vast results; remarkable; strong; powerful; mighty; noble.</defn>
    <defn>Title referring to an important leader.</defn>
    <defn>Doing or exemplifying (a characteristic or pursuit) on a large scale; active or enthusiastic.</defn>
    <defn>(often followed by 'at') Skilful or adroit.</defn>
    <defn>Very good; excellent; wonderful; fantastic (from 1848).</defn>
    <defn>Intensifying a word or expression, used in mild oaths.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>group</word>
    <defn>A number of things or persons being in some relation to one another.</defn>
    <defn>A set with an associative binary operation, under which there exists an identity element, and such that each element has an inverse.</defn>
    <defn>An effective divisor on a curve.</defn>
    <defn>A small number (up to about fifty) of galaxies that are near each other.</defn>
    <defn>A column in the periodic table of chemical elements.</defn>
    <defn>A subset of a culture or of a society.</defn>
    <defn>An air force formation.</defn>
    <defn>A collection of formations or rock strata.</defn>
    <defn>A number of users with same rights with respect to accession, modification, and execution of files, computers and peripherals.</defn>
    <defn>An element of an espresso machine from which hot water pours into the portafilter.</defn>
    <defn>A number of eighth, sixteenth, etc., notes joined at the stems; sometimes rather indefinitely applied to any ornament made up of a few short notes.</defn>
    <defn>A set of teams playing each other in the same division, while not during the same period playing any teams that belong to other sets in the division.</defn>
    <defn>A commercial organization.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>guard</word>
    <defn>A person who, or thing that, protects or watches over something.</defn>
    <defn>A garda; a police officer.</defn>
    <defn>A squad responsible for protecting something.</defn>
    <defn>The part of a sword that protects the wielder's hand.</defn>
    <defn>A part of a machine which blocks access to dangerous parts.</defn>
    <defn>A watchchain.</defn>
    <defn>A panel of a car that encloses the wheel area, especially the front wheels.</defn>
    <defn>A state of caution; posture of defence.</defn>
    <defn>Something worn to protect part of the body, e.g. the shins in cricket.</defn>
    <defn>A relatively short player, playing farther from the basket than a forward or center.</defn>
    <defn>Either of two offensive positions between the center and each of the offensive tackles, whose main responsibilities are to protect the quarterback, and open up "holes" through which offensive players can run.</defn>
    <defn>An employee, normally travelling in the last vehicle of a train, responsible for the safety of the train.</defn>
    <defn>A Boolean expression that must evaluate to true for a branch of program execution to continue.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>guide</word>
    <defn>Any marking or object that catches the eye to provide quick reference.</defn>
    <defn>A spirit believed to speak through a medium.</defn>
    <defn>A member of a group marching in formation who sets the pattern of movement or alignment for the rest.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>guideline</word>
    <defn>A non-specific rule or principle that provides direction to action or behaviour.</defn>
    <defn>A plan or explanation to guide one in setting standards or determining a course of action.</defn>
    <defn>A light line, used in lettering, to help align the text.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>hand</word>
    <defn>The part of the forelimb below the forearm or wrist in a human, and the corresponding part in many other animals.</defn>
    <defn>In linear measurement:</defn>
    <defn>A side; part, camp; direction, either right or left.</defn>
    <defn>Power of performance; means of execution; ability; skill; dexterity.</defn>
    <defn>An agent; a servant, or manual laborer, especially in compounds; a workman, trained or competent for special service or duty; a performer more or less skillful.</defn>
    <defn>An instance of helping.</defn>
    <defn>Handwriting; style of penmanship.</defn>
    <defn>A person's autograph or signature.</defn>
    <defn>Personal possession; ownership.</defn>
    <defn>Applause.</defn>
    <defn>A whole rhizome of ginger.</defn>
    <defn>The feel of a fabric; the impression or quality of the fabric as judged qualitatively by the sense of touch.</defn>
    <defn>Actual performance; deed; act; workmanship; agency; hence, manner of performance.</defn>
    <defn>Agency in transmission from one person to another.</defn>
    <defn>Rate; price.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>he</word>
    <defn>A male.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>heart</word>
    <defn>A muscular organ that pumps blood through the body, traditionally thought to be the seat of emotion.</defn>
    <defn>Emotions, kindness, moral effort, or spirit in general.</defn>
    <defn>The seat of the affections or sensibilities, collectively or separately, as love, hate, joy, grief, courage, etc.; rarely, the seat of the understanding or will; usually in a good sense; personality.</defn>
    <defn>Courage; courageous purpose; spirit.</defn>
    <defn>Vigorous and efficient activity; power of fertile production; condition of the soil, whether good or bad.</defn>
    <defn>A term of affectionate or kindly and familiar address.</defn>
    <defn>Personality, disposition.</defn>
    <defn>A wight or being.</defn>
    <defn>The twenty-fourth Lenormand card.</defn>
    <defn>The centre, essence, or core.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>helpful</word>
    <defn>Furnishing help; giving aid; useful.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>hero</word>
    <defn>Somebody who possesses great bravery and carries out extraordinary or noble deeds.</defn>
    <defn>A role model.</defn>
    <defn>The protagonist in a work of fiction.</defn>
    <defn>(food styling) The product chosen from several candidates to be photographed.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>hi</word>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>highway</word>
    <defn>A motor vehicle for transporting large numbers of people along roads.</defn>
    <defn>An electrical conductor or interface serving as a common connection for two or more circuits or components.</defn>
    <defn>(medical industry) An ambulance.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>hole</word>
    <defn>A hollow place or cavity; an excavation; a pit; an opening in or through a solid body, a fabric, etc.; a perforation; a rent; a fissure.</defn>
    <defn>(heading) In games.</defn>
    <defn>An excavation pit or trench.</defn>
    <defn>A weakness; a flaw or ambiguity.</defn>
    <defn>A container or receptacle.</defn>
    <defn>In semiconductors, a lack of an electron in an occupied band behaving like a positively charged particle.</defn>
    <defn>A security vulnerability in software which can be taken advantage of by an exploit.</defn>
    <defn>An orifice, in particular the anus. When used with shut it always refers to the mouth.</defn>
    <defn>(with "the") Solitary confinement, a high-security prison cell often used as punishment.</defn>
    <defn>An undesirable place to live or visit; a hovel.</defn>
    <defn>Difficulty, in particular, debt.</defn>
    <defn>A chordless cycle in a graph.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>home</word>
    <defn>A dwelling.</defn>
    <defn>One&#8217;s native land; the place or country in which one dwells; the place where one&#8217;s ancestors dwell or dwelt.</defn>
    <defn>The locality where a thing is usually found, or was first found, or where it is naturally abundant; habitat; seat.</defn>
    <defn>A focus point.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>honor</word>
    <defn>Recognition of importance or value; respect; veneration (of someone, usually for being morally upright or successful)</defn>
    <defn>The state of being morally upright, honest, noble, virtuous, and magnanimous; excellence of character; the perception of such a state; favourable reputation; dignity</defn>
    <defn>A token of praise or respect; something that represents praiseworthiness or respect, such as a prize or award given by the state to a citizen</defn>
    <defn>A privilege</defn>
    <defn>(in the plural) the privilege of going first</defn>
    <defn>A cause of respect and fame; a glory; an excellency; an ornament.</defn>
    <defn>(feudal law) a seigniory or lordship held of the king, on which other lordships and manors depended</defn>
    <defn>The center point of the upper half of an armorial escutcheon (compare honour point)</defn>
    <defn>In bridge, an ace, king, queen, jack, or ten especially of the trump suit. In some other games, an ace, king, queen or jack.</defn>
    <defn>(in the plural) (courses for) an honours degree: a university qualification of the highest rank</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>horror</word>
    <defn>An intense distressing emotion of fear or repugnance.</defn>
    <defn>Intense dislike or aversion; an abhorrence.</defn>
    <defn>A genre of fiction designed to evoke a feeling of fear and suspense.</defn>
    <defn>An individual work in this genre.</defn>
    <defn>A nasty or ill-behaved person; a rascal or terror.</defn>
    <defn>(plural) Delirium tremens.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>hundred</word>
    <defn>An administrative subdivision of southern English counties formerly reckoned as comprising 100 hides (households or families) and notionally equal to 12,000 acres.</defn>
    <defn>(by extension) Similar divisions in other areas, particularly in other areas of Britain or the British Empire</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>hungry</word>
    <defn>Affected by hunger; desiring of food; having a physical need for food.</defn>
    <defn>Causing hunger</defn>
    <defn>Eager, having an avid desire (&#8216;appetite&#8217;) for something.</defn>
    <defn>Not rich or fertile; poor; barren; starved.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>hurt</word>
    <defn>An emotional or psychological humiliation or bad experience.</defn>
    <defn>A bodily injury causing pain; a wound or bruise.</defn>
    <defn>Injury; damage; detriment; harm</defn>
    <defn>A roundel azure (blue circular spot).</defn>
    <defn>A band on a trip-hammer helve, bearing the trunnions.</defn>
    <defn>A husk.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>idea</word>
    <defn>An abstract archetype of a given thing, compared to which real-life examples are seen as imperfect approximations; pure essence, as opposed to actual examples.</defn>
    <defn>The form or shape of something; a quintessential aspect or characteristic.</defn>
    <defn>An image of an object that is formed in the mind or recalled by the memory.</defn>
    <defn>More generally, any result of mental activity; a thought, a notion; a way of thinking.</defn>
    <defn>A conception in the mind of something to be done; a plan for doing something, an intention.</defn>
    <defn>A purposeful aim or goal; intent</defn>
    <defn>A vague or fanciful notion; a feeling or hunch; an impression.</defn>
    <defn>A musical theme or melodic subject.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>imagination</word>
    <defn>The image-making power of the mind; the act of mentally creating or reproducing an object not previously perceived; the ability to create such images.</defn>
    <defn>Particularly, construction of false images; fantasizing.</defn>
    <defn>Creativity; resourcefulness.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>implication</word>
    <defn>The act of implicating.</defn>
    <defn>The state of being implicated.</defn>
    <defn>(usually in the plural) A possible effect or result of a decision or action.</defn>
    <defn>An implying, or that which is implied, but not expressed; an inference, or something which may fairly be understood, though not expressed in words.</defn>
    <defn>The connective in propositional calculus that, when joining two predicates A and B in that order, has the meaning "if A is true, then B is true".</defn>
    <defn>Logical consequence.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>importance</word>
    <defn>The quality or condition of being important or worthy of note.</defn>
    <defn>Significance or prominence.</defn>
    <defn>Personal status or standing.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>impress</word>
    <defn>Characteristic; mark of distinction; stamp.</defn>
    <defn>A heraldic device; an impresa.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>incident</word>
    <defn>An event or occurrence.</defn>
    <defn>An event that causes or may cause an interruption or a crisis, such as a workplace illness or a software error.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>including</word>
    <defn>To bring into a group, class, set, or total as a (new) part or member.</defn>
    <defn>To contain, as parts of a whole; to comprehend.</defn>
    <defn>To enclose, confine.</defn>
    <defn>To conclude; to terminate.</defn>
    <defn>To use a directive that allows the use of source code from another file.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>income</word>
    <defn>Money one earns by working or by capitalising on the work of others.</defn>
    <defn>Money coming in to a fund, account, or policy.</defn>
    <defn>A coming in; arrival; entrance; introduction.</defn>
    <defn>An entrance-fee.</defn>
    <defn>A coming in as by influx or inspiration, hence, an inspired quality or characteristic, as courage or zeal; an inflowing principle.</defn>
    <defn>A disease or ailment without known or apparent cause, as distinguished from one induced by accident or contagion; an oncome.</defn>
    <defn>That which is taken into the body as food; the ingesta; sometimes restricted to the nutritive, or digestible, portion of the food.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>individual</word>
    <defn>A person considered alone, rather than as belonging to a group of people.</defn>
    <defn>A single physical human being as a legal subject, as opposed to a legal person such as a corporation.</defn>
    <defn>An object, be it a thing or an agent, as contrasted to a class.</defn>
    <defn>An element belonging to a population.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>initial</word>
    <defn>The first letter of a word or a name.</defn>
    <defn>In plural, the first letter of each word of a person's full name considered as a unit.</defn>
    <defn>Onset, part of a syllable that precedes the syllable nucleus in phonetics and phonology.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>inside</word>
    <defn>The interior or inner part.</defn>
    <defn>The left-hand side of a road if one drives on the left, or right-hand side if one drives on the right.</defn>
    <defn>The side of a curved road, racetrack etc. that has the shorter arc length; the side of a racetrack nearer the interior of the course or some other point of reference.</defn>
    <defn>(in the plural) The interior organs of the body, especially the guts.</defn>
    <defn>A passenger within a coach or carriage, as distinguished from one upon the outside.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>instructor</word>
    <defn>One who instructs; a teacher.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>intellectual</word>
    <defn>An intelligent, learned person, especially one who discourses about learned matters.</defn>
    <defn>The intellect or understanding; mental powers or faculties.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>international</word>
    <defn>Someone who has represented their country in a particular sport.</defn>
    <defn>A game or contest between two or more nations.</defn>
    <defn>A transnational organization of political parties of similar ideology.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>investigate</word>
    <defn>To inquire into or study in order to ascertain facts or information.</defn>
    <defn>To examine, look into, or scrutinize in order to discover something hidden or secret.</defn>
    <defn>To conduct an inquiry or examination.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>investigator</word>
    <defn>One who investigates.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>involved</word>
    <defn>To roll or fold up; to wind round; to entwine.</defn>
    <defn>To envelop completely; to surround; to cover; to hide.</defn>
    <defn>To complicate or make intricate, as in grammatical structure.</defn>
    <defn>To connect with something as a natural or logical consequence or effect; to include necessarily; to imply.</defn>
    <defn>To take in; to gather in; to mingle confusedly; to blend or merge.</defn>
    <defn>To envelop, enfold, entangle.</defn>
    <defn>To engage (someone) to participate in a task.</defn>
    <defn>To raise to any assigned power; to multiply, as a quantity, into itself a given number of times.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>issue</word>
    <defn>The action or an instance of flowing or coming out, an outflow, particularly:</defn>
    <defn>Someone or something that flows out or comes out, particularly:</defn>
    <defn>The means or opportunity by which something flows or comes out, particularly:</defn>
    <defn>The place where something flows or comes out, an outlet, particularly:</defn>
    <defn>The action or an instance of sending something out, particularly:</defn>
    <defn>Any question or situation to be resolved, particularly:</defn>
    <defn>The action or an instance of concluding something, particularly:</defn>
    <defn>The end result of an event or events, any result or outcome, particularly:</defn>
    <defn>The action or an instance of feeling some emotion.</defn>
    <defn>The action or an instance of leaving any state or condition.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>itself</word>
    <defn>(reflexive pronoun) it; A thing as the object of a verb or preposition that also appears as the subject</defn>
    <defn>It; used to intensify the subject, especially to emphasize that it is the only participant in the predicate</defn>
    <defn>It; used to refer back to an earlier subject</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>jet</word>
    <defn>A collimated stream, spurt or flow of liquid or gas from a pressurized container, an engine, etc.</defn>
    <defn>An engine that propels a vehicle using a stream of fluid as propulsion.</defn>
    <defn>A part of a carburetor that controls the amount of fuel mixed with the air.</defn>
    <defn>A narrow cone of hadrons and other particles produced by the hadronization of a quark or gluon.</defn>
    <defn>Drift; scope; range, as of an argument.</defn>
    <defn>The sprue of a type, which is broken from it when the type is cold.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>joke</word>
    <defn>An amusing story.</defn>
    <defn>Something said or done for amusement, not in seriousness.</defn>
    <defn>The root cause or main issue, especially an unexpected one</defn>
    <defn>A laughably worthless thing or person; a sham.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>joy</word>
    <defn>A feeling of extreme happiness or cheerfulness, especially related to the acquisition or expectation of something good.</defn>
    <defn>Anything that causes such a feeling.</defn>
    <defn>Luck or success; a positive outcome.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>justice</word>
    <defn>The state or characteristic of being just or fair.</defn>
    <defn>The ideal of fairness, impartiality, etc., especially with regard to the punishment of wrongdoing.</defn>
    <defn>Judgment and punishment of a party who has allegedly wronged another.</defn>
    <defn>The civil power dealing with law.</defn>
    <defn>A title given to judges of certain courts; capitalized as a title.</defn>
    <defn>Correctness, conforming to reality or rules.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>justify</word>
    <defn>To provide an acceptable explanation for.</defn>
    <defn>To be a good, acceptable reason for; warrant.</defn>
    <defn>To arrange (text) on a page or a computer screen such that the left and right ends of all lines within paragraphs are aligned.</defn>
    <defn>To absolve, and declare to be free of blame or sin.</defn>
    <defn>To give reasons for one&#8217;s actions; to make an argument to prove that one is in the right.</defn>
    <defn>To prove; to ratify; to confirm.</defn>
    <defn>To show (a person) to have had a sufficient legal reason for an act that has been made the subject of a charge or accusation.</defn>
    <defn>To qualify (oneself) as a surety by taking oath to the ownership of sufficient property.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>keep</word>
    <defn>The main tower of a castle or fortress, located within the castle walls.</defn>
    <defn>The state of being kept; hence, the resulting condition; case.</defn>
    <defn>That which is kept in charge; a charge.</defn>
    <defn>A cap for holding something, such as a journal box, in place.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>kind</word>
    <defn>A type, race or category; a group of entities that have common characteristics such that they may be grouped together.</defn>
    <defn>A makeshift or otherwise atypical specimen.</defn>
    <defn>One's inherent nature; character, natural disposition.</defn>
    <defn>Family, lineage.</defn>
    <defn>Manner.</defn>
    <defn>Goods or services used as payment, as e.g. in barter.</defn>
    <defn>Equivalent means used as response to an action.</defn>
    <defn>Each of the two elements of the communion service, bread and wine.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>knife</word>
    <defn>A utensil or a tool designed for cutting, consisting of a flat piece of hard material, usually steel or other metal (the blade), usually sharpened on one edge, attached to a handle. The blade may be pointed for piercing.</defn>
    <defn>A weapon designed with the aforementioned specifications intended for slashing and/or stabbing and too short to be called a sword. A dagger.</defn>
    <defn>Any blade-like part in a tool or a machine designed for cutting, such as that of a chipper.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>lawsuit</word>
    <defn>In civil law, a case where two or more people disagree and one or more of the parties take the case to a court for resolution.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>leader</word>
    <defn>Any person that leads or directs</defn>
    <defn>An animal that leads</defn>
    <defn>Someone or something that leads or conducts</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>learn</word>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>legitimate</word>
    <defn>A person born to a legally married couple.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>liberal</word>
    <defn>Someone left-wing; one with a left-wing ideology.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>limit</word>
    <defn>A restriction; a bound beyond which one may not go.</defn>
    <defn>The cone of a diagram through which any other cone of that same diagram can factor uniquely.</defn>
    <defn>The final, utmost, or furthest point; the border or edge.</defn>
    <defn>That which terminates a period of time; hence, the period itself; the full time or extent.</defn>
    <defn>A restriction; a check or curb; a hindrance.</defn>
    <defn>A determining feature; a distinguishing characteristic.</defn>
    <defn>The first group of riders to depart in a handicap race.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>line</word>
    <defn>A path through two or more points (compare &#8216;segment&#8217;); a continuous mark, including as made by a pen; any path, curved or straight.</defn>
    <defn>A rope, cord, string, or thread, of any thickness.</defn>
    <defn>A hose or pipe, of any size.</defn>
    <defn>Direction, path.</defn>
    <defn>The wire connecting one telegraphic station with another, a telephone or internet cable between two points: a telephone or network connection.</defn>
    <defn>A letter, a written form of communication.</defn>
    <defn>A connected series of public conveyances, as a roadbed or railway track; and hence, an established arrangement for forwarding merchandise, etc.</defn>
    <defn>A trench or rampart, or the non-physical demarcation of the extent of the territory occupied by specified forces.</defn>
    <defn>A long tape or ribbon marked with units for measuring; a tape measure.</defn>
    <defn>A threadlike crease or wrinkle marking the face, hand, or body; hence, a characteristic mark.</defn>
    <defn>Lineament; feature; figure (of one's body).</defn>
    <defn>A more-or-less straight sequence of people, objects, etc., either arranged as a queue or column and often waiting to be processed or dealt with, or arranged abreast of one another in a row (and contrasted with a column), as in a military formation.</defn>
    <defn>The regular infantry of an army, as distinguished from militia, guards, volunteer corps, cavalry, artillery etc.</defn>
    <defn>A small amount of text. Specifically:</defn>
    <defn>Course of conduct, thought, occupation, or policy; method of argument; department of industry, trade, or intellectual activity.</defn>
    <defn>The official, stated position (or set of positions) of an individual or group, particularly a political or religious faction.</defn>
    <defn>A set of products or services sold by a business, or by extension, the business itself.</defn>
    <defn>A number of shares taken by a jobber.</defn>
    <defn>A measure of length:</defn>
    <defn>A maxwell, a unit of magnetic flux.</defn>
    <defn>(1800s, with "the") The batter&#8217;s box.</defn>
    <defn>The position in which the fencers hold their swords.</defn>
    <defn>Proper relative position or adjustment (of parts, not as to design or proportion, but with reference to smooth working).</defn>
    <defn>A small path-shaped portion or serving of a powdery illegal drug, especially cocaine.</defn>
    <defn>Instruction; doctrine.</defn>
    <defn>Population of cells derived from a single cell and containing the same genetic makeup.</defn>
    <defn>A group of forwards that play together.</defn>
    <defn>A vascular catheter.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>lip</word>
    <defn>Either of the two fleshy protrusions around the opening of the mouth.</defn>
    <defn>(by extension) The projecting rim of an open container; a short open spout.</defn>
    <defn>Backtalk; verbal impertinence.</defn>
    <defn>The edge of a high spot of land.</defn>
    <defn>The sharp cutting edge on the end of an auger.</defn>
    <defn>One of the two opposite divisions of a labiate corolla.</defn>
    <defn>The distinctive petal of the Orchis family.</defn>
    <defn>One of the edges of the aperture of a univalve shell.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>list</word>
    <defn>A strip of fabric, especially from the edge of a piece of cloth.</defn>
    <defn>Material used for cloth selvage.</defn>
    <defn>A register or roll of paper consisting of a compilation or enumeration of a set of possible items; the compilation or enumeration itself.</defn>
    <defn>(in the plural) The barriers or palisades used to fence off a space for jousting or tilting tournaments.</defn>
    <defn>A narrow strip of wood, especially sapwood, cut from the edge of a board or plank.</defn>
    <defn>(ropemaking) A piece of woollen cloth with which the yarns are grasped by a worker.</defn>
    <defn>(tin-plate manufacture) The first thin coating of tin; a wire-like rim of tin left on an edge of the plate after it is coated.</defn>
    <defn>A stripe.</defn>
    <defn>A boundary or limit; a border.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>location</word>
    <defn>A particular point or place in physical space.</defn>
    <defn>An act of locating.</defn>
    <defn>An apartheid-era urban area populated by non-white people; township.</defn>
    <defn>A leasing on rent.</defn>
    <defn>A contract for the use of a thing, or service of a person, for hire.</defn>
    <defn>The marking out of the boundaries, or identifying the place or site of, a piece of land, according to the description given in an entry, plan, map, etc.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>long</word>
    <defn>A note formerly used in music, one half the length of a large, twice that of a breve.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>long-term</word>
    <defn>Becoming evident after a relatively long time period.</defn>
    <defn>Extending over a relatively long time period.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>loss</word>
    <defn>The result of no longer possessing an object, a function, or a characteristic due to external causes or misplacement.</defn>
    <defn>The destruction or ruin of an object.</defn>
    <defn>Something that has been destroyed or ruined.</defn>
    <defn>Defeat; an instance of being defeated.</defn>
    <defn>The death of a person or animal.</defn>
    <defn>The condition of grief caused by losing someone or something, especially someone who has died.</defn>
    <defn>(financial) The sum an entity loses on balance.</defn>
    <defn>Electricity of kinetic power expended without doing useful work.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>lost</word>
    <defn>To cause (something) to cease to be in one's possession or capability due to unfortunate or unknown circumstances, events or reasons.</defn>
    <defn>To wander from; to miss, so as not to be able to find; to go astray from.</defn>
    <defn>To fail to win (a game, competition, trial, etc).</defn>
    <defn>To be unable to follow or trace (somebody or something) any longer.</defn>
    <defn>To cause (somebody) to be unable to follow or trace one any longer.</defn>
    <defn>To cease exhibiting; to overcome (a behavior or emotion).</defn>
    <defn>To shed, remove, discard, or eliminate.</defn>
    <defn>Of a clock, to run slower than expected.</defn>
    <defn>(ditransitive) To cause (someone) the loss of something; to deprive of.</defn>
    <defn>To fail to catch with the mind or senses; to miss.</defn>
    <defn>To cause to part with; to deprive of.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>luck</word>
    <defn>Something that happens to someone by chance, a chance occurrence, especially a favourable one.</defn>
    <defn>A superstitious feeling that brings fortune or success.</defn>
    <defn>Success.</defn>
    <defn>The results of a random number generator.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>lunch</word>
    <defn>A light meal usually eaten around midday, notably when not as main meal of the day.</defn>
    <defn>A break in play between the first and second sessions.</defn>
    <defn>(Minnesota) Any small meal, especially one eaten at a social gathering.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>mad</word>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>mainly</word>
    <defn>Forcefully, vigorously.</defn>
    <defn>Of the production of a sound: loudly, powerfully.</defn>
    <defn>To a great degree; very much.</defn>
    <defn>Chiefly; for the most part.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>majority</word>
    <defn>More than half (50%) of some group.</defn>
    <defn>The difference between the winning vote and the rest of the votes.</defn>
    <defn>Legal adulthood.</defn>
    <defn>The office held by a member of the armed forces in the rank of major.</defn>
    <defn>Ancestors; ancestry.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>mall</word>
    <defn>A pedestrianised street, especially a shopping precinct.</defn>
    <defn>An enclosed shopping centre.</defn>
    <defn>A public walk; a level shaded walk, a promenade.</defn>
    <defn>The game of polo.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>manager</word>
    <defn>A person whose job is to manage something, such as a business, a restaurant, or a sports team.</defn>
    <defn>The head coach.</defn>
    <defn>An administrator, for a singer or group.</defn>
    <defn>(computer software) A window or application whose purpose is to give the user the control over some aspect of the system.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>mean</word>
    <defn>To lament.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>meanwhile</word>
    <defn>The time between two events.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>medicine</word>
    <defn>A substance which specifically promotes healing when ingested or consumed in some way.</defn>
    <defn>A treatment or cure.</defn>
    <defn>The study of the cause, diagnosis, prognosis and treatment of disease or illness.</defn>
    <defn>Among the Native Americans, any object supposed to give control over natural or magical forces, to act as a protective charm, or to cause healing.</defn>
    <defn>Black magic, superstition.</defn>
    <defn>A philter or love potion.</defn>
    <defn>A physician.</defn>
    <defn>Recreational drugs, especially alcoholic drinks.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>menu</word>
    <defn>The details of the food to be served at a banquet; a bill of fare.</defn>
    <defn>A list of dishes offered in a restaurant.</defn>
    <defn>A list from which the user may select an operation to be performed, often done with a keyboard, mouse, or controller under a graphical user interface</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>message</word>
    <defn>A communication, or what is communicated; any concept or information conveyed.</defn>
    <defn>An underlying theme or conclusion to be drawn from something.</defn>
    <defn>(chiefly in the plural) An errand.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>metal</word>
    <defn>(heading) Chemical elements or alloys, and the mines where their ores come from.</defn>
    <defn>A light tincture used in a coat of arms, specifically argent and or.</defn>
    <defn>Molten glass that is to be blown or moulded to form objects.</defn>
    <defn>The substance that constitutes something or someone; matter; hence, character or temper; mettle.</defn>
    <defn>The effective power or calibre of guns carried by a vessel of war.</defn>
    <defn>(in the plural) The rails of a railway.</defn>
    <defn>(travel) The actual airline operating a flight, rather than any of the codeshare operators.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>mine</word>
    <defn>My; belonging to me; that which belongs to me.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>mission</word>
    <defn>A set of tasks that fulfills a purpose or duty; an assignment set by an employer, or by oneself.</defn>
    <defn>Religious evangelism.</defn>
    <defn>(Catholic tradition) an infrequent gathering of religious believers in a parish, usually part of a larger regional event with a central theme.</defn>
    <defn>A number of people appointed to perform any service; a delegation; an embassy.</defn>
    <defn>Dismissal; discharge from service</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>mom</word>
    <defn>(familiar) mother.</defn>
    <defn>An adult female owner of a pet.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>moment</word>
    <defn>A brief, unspecified amount of time.</defn>
    <defn>The smallest portion of time; an instant.</defn>
    <defn>Weight or importance.</defn>
    <defn>The turning effect of a force applied to a rotational system at a distance from the axis of rotation.</defn>
    <defn>(unit) A definite period of time, specifically one-tenth of a point, or one-fortieth or one-fiftieth of an hour.</defn>
    <defn>A petit mal episode; such a spell.</defn>
    <defn>A fit; a brief tantrum.</defn>
    <defn>An infinitesimal change in a varying quantity; an increment or decrement.</defn>
    <defn>A quantitative measure of the shape of a set of points.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>money</word>
    <defn>A legally or socially binding conceptual contract of entitlement to wealth, void of intrinsic value, payable for all debts and taxes, and regulated in supply.</defn>
    <defn>A generally accepted means of exchange and measure of value.</defn>
    <defn>A currency maintained by a state or other entity which can guarantee its value (such as a monetary union).</defn>
    <defn>Hard cash in the form of banknotes and coins, as opposed to cheques/checks, credit cards, or credit more generally.</defn>
    <defn>The total value of liquid assets available for an individual or other economic unit, such as cash and bank deposits.</defn>
    <defn>Wealth; a person, family or class that possesses wealth</defn>
    <defn>An item of value between two or more parties used for the exchange of goods or services.</defn>
    <defn>A person who funds an operation.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>monitor</word>
    <defn>Someone who watches over something; a person in charge of something or someone.</defn>
    <defn>A device that detects and informs on the presence, quantity, etc., of something.</defn>
    <defn>A device similar to a television set used as to give a graphical display of the output from a computer.</defn>
    <defn>A program for viewing and editing.</defn>
    <defn>A student leader in a class.</defn>
    <defn>One of a class of relatively small armored warships designed for shore bombardment or riverine warfare rather than combat with other ships.</defn>
    <defn>An ironclad.</defn>
    <defn>One who admonishes; one who warns of faults, informs of duty, or gives advice and instruction by way of reproof or caution.</defn>
    <defn>A tool holder, as for a lathe, shaped like a low turret, and capable of being revolved on a vertical pivot so as to bring the several tools successively into position.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>mood</word>
    <defn>A mental or emotional state, composure.</defn>
    <defn>Emotional character (of a work of music, literature, or other art).</defn>
    <defn>A disposition to do something, a state of mind receptive or disposed to do something.</defn>
    <defn>A prevalent atmosphere, attitude, or feeling.</defn>
    <defn>A familiar, relatable feeling, experience, or thing.</defn>
    <defn>Courage, heart, valor; also vim and vigor.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>moon</word>
    <defn>The god of the Moon in Heathenry.</defn>
    <defn>A surname.</defn>
    <defn>The 54th sura (chapter) of the Qur'an.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>mortgage</word>
    <defn>A special form of secured loan where the purpose of the loan must be specified to the lender, to purchase assets that must be fixed (not movable) property, such as a house or piece of farm land. The assets are registered as the legal property of the borrower but the lender can seize them and dispose of them if they are not satisfied with the manner in which the repayment of the loan is conducted by the borrower. Once the loan is fully repaid, the lender loses this right of seizure and the assets are then deemed to be unencumbered.</defn>
    <defn>State of being pledged.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>mostly</word>
    <defn>Mainly or chiefly; for the most part; usually, generally, on the whole.</defn>
    <defn>To the greatest extent; most.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>mouth</word>
    <defn>The opening of a creature through which food is ingested.</defn>
    <defn>The end of a river out of which water flows into a sea or other large body of water.</defn>
    <defn>An outlet, aperture or orifice.</defn>
    <defn>A loud or overly talkative person.</defn>
    <defn>Cry; voice.</defn>
    <defn>Speech; language; testimony.</defn>
    <defn>A wry face; a grimace; a mow.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>move</word>
    <defn>An act for the attainment of an object; a step in the execution of a plan or purpose.</defn>
    <defn>A formalized or practiced action used in athletics, dance, physical exercise, self-defense, hand-to-hand combat, etc.</defn>
    <defn>The event of changing one's residence.</defn>
    <defn>A change in strategy.</defn>
    <defn>A transfer, a change from one employer to another.</defn>
    <defn>The act of moving a token on a gameboard from one position to another according to the rules of the game.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>multiple</word>
    <defn>A whole number that can be divided by another number with no remainder.</defn>
    <defn>Price-earnings ratio.</defn>
    <defn>One of a set of the same thing; a duplicate.</defn>
    <defn>A chain store.</defn>
    <defn>A discovery resulting from the work of many people throughout history, not merely the work of the person who makes the final connection.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>must</word>
    <defn>Something that is mandatory or required.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>negotiate</word>
    <defn>To confer with others in order to come to terms or reach an agreement.</defn>
    <defn>To arrange or settle something by mutual agreement.</defn>
    <defn>To succeed in coping with, or getting over something.</defn>
    <defn>To transfer to another person with all the rights of the original holder; to pass, as a bill.</defn>
    <defn>To transact business; to carry on trade.</defn>
    <defn>To intrigue; to scheme.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>nerve</word>
    <defn>A bundle of neurons with their connective tissue sheaths, blood vessels and lymphatics.</defn>
    <defn>A neuron.</defn>
    <defn>A vein in a leaf; a grain in wood</defn>
    <defn>Courage, boldness.</defn>
    <defn>Patience.</defn>
    <defn>Stamina, endurance, fortitude.</defn>
    <defn>Audacity, gall.</defn>
    <defn>(polymer technology) The elastic resistance of raw rubber or other polymers to permanent deformation during processing.</defn>
    <defn>(in the plural) Agitation caused by fear, stress or other negative emotion.</defn>
    <defn>Sinew, tendon.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>nine</word>
    <defn>The digit or figure 9.</defn>
    <defn>(usually in the plural) A statistical unit of proportion (of reliability, purity, etc.).</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>nomination</word>
    <defn>An act or instance of nominating.</defn>
    <defn>A device or means by which a person or thing is nominated.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>number</word>
    <defn>An abstract entity used to describe quantity.</defn>
    <defn>A numeral: a symbol for a non-negative integer.</defn>
    <defn>(Followed by a numeral; used attributively) Indicating the position of something in a list or sequence. Abbreviations: No or No., no or no. (in each case, sometimes written with a superscript "o", like N&#186; or &#8470;). The symbol "#" is also used in this manner.</defn>
    <defn>Quantity.</defn>
    <defn>A sequence of digits and letters used to register people, automobiles, and various other items.</defn>
    <defn>(grammar) Of a word or phrase, the state of being singular, dual or plural, shown by inflection.</defn>
    <defn>(in the plural) Poetic metres; verses, rhymes.</defn>
    <defn>A performance; especially, a single song or song and dance routine within a larger show.</defn>
    <defn>A person.</defn>
    <defn>An item of clothing, particularly a stylish one.</defn>
    <defn>A marijuana cigarette, or joint; also, a quantity of marijuana bought form a dealer.</defn>
    <defn>An issue of a periodical publication.</defn>
    <defn>A large amount, in contrast to a smaller amount; numerical preponderance.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>odd</word>
    <defn>Something left over, not forming part of a set.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>offer</word>
    <defn>A proposal that has been made.</defn>
    <defn>An invitation to enter into a binding contract communicated to another party which contains terms sufficiently definite to create an enforceable contract if the other party accepts the invitation.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>okay</word>
    <defn>Endorsement; approval.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>old</word>
    <defn>(in combination) One of a specified age.</defn>
    <defn>(most often plural) One's parents.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>ongoing</word>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>opinion</word>
    <defn>A subjective belief, judgment or perspective that a person has formed about a topic, issue, person or thing.</defn>
    <defn>The judgment or sentiment which the mind forms of persons or things; estimation.</defn>
    <defn>Favorable estimation; hence, consideration; reputation; fame; public sentiment or esteem.</defn>
    <defn>Obstinacy in holding to one's belief or impression; opiniativeness; conceitedness.</defn>
    <defn>The formal decision, or expression of views, of a judge, an umpire, a doctor, or other party officially called upon to consider and decide upon a matter or point submitted.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>opponent</word>
    <defn>One who opposes another; one who works or takes a position against someone or something; one who attempts to stop the progress of someone or something.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>option</word>
    <defn>One of a set of choices that can be made.</defn>
    <defn>The freedom or right to choose.</defn>
    <defn>A contract giving the holder the right to buy or sell an asset at a set strike price; can apply to financial market transactions, or to ordinary transactions for tangible assets such as a residence or automobile.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>or</word>
    <defn>Otherwise (a consequence of the condition that the previous is false).</defn>
    <defn>Connects two equivalent names.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>originally</word>
    <defn>As it was in the beginning.</defn>
    <defn>In an original manner.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>otherwise</word>
    <defn>Other than supposed; different.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>ourselves</word>
    <defn>(reflexive pronoun) Us; the group including the speaker as the object of a verb or preposition when that group also is the subject.</defn>
    <defn>We; intensifies the subject as the group including the speaker, especially to indicate that no one else satisfies the predicate.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>outcome</word>
    <defn>That which is produced or occurs as a result of an event or process.</defn>
    <defn>The result of a random trial. An element of a sample space.</defn>
    <defn>The scoreline; the result.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>outside</word>
    <defn>The part of something that faces out; the outer surface.</defn>
    <defn>The external appearance of someone or something.</defn>
    <defn>The space beyond some limit or boundary.</defn>
    <defn>The furthest limit, as to number, quantity, extent, etc.</defn>
    <defn>The part of a road towards the central division: towards the right if one drives on the left, or towards the left if one drives on the right.</defn>
    <defn>The side of a curved road, racetrack etc. that has the longer arc length; the side of a racetrack furthest from the interior of the course or some other point of reference.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>over</word>
    <defn>A set of six legal balls bowled.</defn>
    <defn>Any surplus amount of money, goods delivered, etc.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>overall</word>
    <defn>(in the plural) A garment, worn for manual labor, with an integral covering extending to the chest, supported by straps.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>overcome</word>
    <defn>The burden or recurring theme in a song.</defn>
    <defn>A surplus.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>overlook</word>
    <defn>A vista or point that gives a beautiful view.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>package</word>
    <defn>Something which is packed, a parcel, a box, an envelope.</defn>
    <defn>Something which consists of various components, such as a piece of computer software.</defn>
    <defn>The act of packing something.</defn>
    <defn>A football formation.</defn>
    <defn>The male genitalia.</defn>
    <defn>A charge made for packing goods.</defn>
    <defn>A group of related stories spread over several pages.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>pain</word>
    <defn>An ache or bodily suffering, or an instance of this; an unpleasant sensation, resulting from a derangement of functions, disease, or injury by violence; hurt.</defn>
    <defn>The condition or fact of suffering or anguish especially mental, as opposed to pleasure; torment; distress</defn>
    <defn>Suffering inflicted as punishment or penalty.</defn>
    <defn>(chiefly in the plural) Labour; effort; great care or trouble taken in doing something.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>pair</word>
    <defn>Two similar or identical things taken together; often followed by of.</defn>
    <defn>Two people in a relationship, partnership or friendship.</defn>
    <defn>Used with binary nouns (often in the plural to indicate multiple instances, since such nouns are plural only, except in some technical contexts)</defn>
    <defn>A couple of working animals attached to work together, as by a yoke.</defn>
    <defn>A poker hand that contains two cards of identical rank, which cannot also count as a better hand.</defn>
    <defn>A score of zero runs (a duck) in both innings of a two-innings match.</defn>
    <defn>A double play, two outs recorded in one play.</defn>
    <defn>A doubleheader, two games played on the same day between the same teams</defn>
    <defn>A boat for two sweep rowers.</defn>
    <defn>The exclusion of one member of a parliamentary party from a vote, if a member of the other party is absent for important personal reasons.</defn>
    <defn>Two members of opposite parties or opinion, as in a parliamentary body, who mutually agree not to vote on a given question, or on issues of a party nature during a specified time.</defn>
    <defn>A number of things resembling one another, or belonging together; a set.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>palm</word>
    <defn>Any of various evergreen trees from the family Palmae or Arecaceae, which are mainly found in the tropics.</defn>
    <defn>(by extension) Triumph; victory.</defn>
    <defn>Any of 23 awards that can be earned after obtaining the Eagle Scout rank, but generally only before turning 18 years old.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>passion</word>
    <defn>Any great, strong, powerful emotion, especially romantic love or extreme hate.</defn>
    <defn>Fervor, determination.</defn>
    <defn>Sexual intercourse, especially when very emotional.</defn>
    <defn>(usually capitalized) The suffering of Jesus leading up to and during his crucifixion.</defn>
    <defn>A display, musical composition, or play meant to commemorate the suffering of Jesus.</defn>
    <defn>Suffering or enduring of imposed or inflicted pain; any suffering or distress.</defn>
    <defn>The state of being acted upon; subjection to an external agent or influence; a passive condition</defn>
    <defn>The capacity of being affected by external agents; susceptibility of impressions from external agents.</defn>
    <defn>An innate attribute, property, or quality of a thing.</defn>
    <defn>Disorder of the mind; madness.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>path</word>
    <defn>A trail for the use of, or worn by, pedestrians.</defn>
    <defn>A course taken.</defn>
    <defn>A Pagan tradition, for example witchcraft, Wicca, druidism, Heathenry.</defn>
    <defn>A metaphorical course.</defn>
    <defn>A method or direction of proceeding.</defn>
    <defn>A human-readable specification for a location within a hierarchical or tree-like structure, such as a file system or as part of a URL.</defn>
    <defn>A continuous map f from the unit interval I = [0,1] to a topological space X.</defn>
    <defn>A slot available for allocation to a railway train over a given route in between other trains.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>people</word>
    <defn>Used as plural of person; a body of human beings considered generally or collectively; a group of two or more persons.</defn>
    <defn>Persons forming or belonging to a particular group, such as a nation, class, ethnic group, country, family, etc.</defn>
    <defn>A group of persons regarded as being employees, followers, companions or subjects of a ruler.</defn>
    <defn>One's colleagues or employees.</defn>
    <defn>A person's ancestors, relatives or family.</defn>
    <defn>The mass of a community as distinguished from a special class (elite); the commonalty; the populace; the vulgar; the common crowd; the citizens.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>performance</word>
    <defn>The act of performing; carrying into execution or action; execution; achievement; accomplishment; representation by action.</defn>
    <defn>That which is performed or accomplished; a thing done or carried through; an achievement; a deed; an act; a feat; especially, an action of an elaborate or public character.</defn>
    <defn>A live show or concert.</defn>
    <defn>The amount of useful work accomplished estimated in terms of time needed, resources used, etc.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>permit</word>
    <defn>An artifact or document rendering something allowed or legal.</defn>
    <defn>Formal permission.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>persuade</word>
    <defn>To successfully convince (someone) to agree to, accept, or do something, usually through reasoning and verbal influence.</defn>
    <defn>To convince of by argument, or by reasons offered or suggested from reflection, etc.; to cause to believe (something).</defn>
    <defn>To urge, plead; to try to convince (someone to do something).</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>physically</word>
    <defn>In a physical manner.</defn>
    <defn>According to the laws of physics.</defn>
    <defn>Using physical force.</defn>
    <defn>According to the rules of medicine.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>pie</word>
    <defn>A type of pastry that consists of an outer crust and a filling.</defn>
    <defn>Any of various other, non-pastry dishes that maintain the general concept of a shell with a filling.</defn>
    <defn>(Northeastern US) A pizza.</defn>
    <defn>The whole of a wealth or resource, to be divided in parts.</defn>
    <defn>(letterpress) A disorderly mess of spilt type.</defn>
    <defn>An especially badly bowled ball.</defn>
    <defn>The vulva.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>pilot</word>
    <defn>A person who steers a ship, a helmsman.</defn>
    <defn>A person who knows well the depths and currents of a harbor or coastal area, who is hired by a vessel to help navigate the harbor or coast.</defn>
    <defn>A guide book for maritime navigation.</defn>
    <defn>An instrument for detecting the compass error.</defn>
    <defn>A person authorised to drive such a vehicle during an escort.</defn>
    <defn>A guide or escort through an unknown or dangerous area.</defn>
    <defn>Something serving as a test or trial.</defn>
    <defn>A person who is in charge of the controls of an aircraft.</defn>
    <defn>A sample episode of a proposed TV series produced to decide if it should be made or not. If approved, typically the first episode of an actual TV series.</defn>
    <defn>A cowcatcher.</defn>
    <defn>One who flies a kite.</defn>
    <defn>A short plug, sometimes made interchangeable, at the end of a counterbore to guide the tool.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>pipe</word>
    <defn>Meanings relating to a wind instrument.</defn>
    <defn>Meanings relating to a hollow conduit.</defn>
    <defn>Meanings relating to a container.</defn>
    <defn>Meanings relating to something resembling a tube.</defn>
    <defn>Meanings relating to computing.</defn>
    <defn>Meanings relating to a smoking implement.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>plan</word>
    <defn>A drawing showing technical details of a building, machine, etc., with unwanted details omitted, and often using symbols rather than detailed drawing to represent doors, valves, etc.</defn>
    <defn>A set of intended actions, usually mutually related, through which one expects to achieve a goal.</defn>
    <defn>A two-dimensional drawing of a building as seen from above with obscuring or irrelevant details such as roof removed, or of a floor of a building, revealing the internal layout; as distinct from the elevation.</defn>
    <defn>A method; a way of procedure; a custom.</defn>
    <defn>A subscription to a service.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>player</word>
    <defn>One that plays</defn>
    <defn>One who is playful; one without serious aims; an idler; a trifler.</defn>
    <defn>A significant participant.</defn>
    <defn>A person who plays the field rather than having a long-term sexual relationship.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>please</word>
    <defn>To make happy or satisfy; to give pleasure to.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>plot</word>
    <defn>(authorship) The course of a story, comprising a series of incidents which are gradually unfolded, sometimes by unexpected means.</defn>
    <defn>An area or land used for building on or planting on.</defn>
    <defn>A graph or diagram drawn by hand or produced by a mechanical or electronic device.</defn>
    <defn>A secret plan to achieve an end, the end or means usually being illegal or otherwise questionable.</defn>
    <defn>Participation in any stratagem or conspiracy.</defn>
    <defn>A plan; a purpose.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>pocket</word>
    <defn>A bag stitched to an item of clothing, used for carrying small items.</defn>
    <defn>Such a receptacle seen as housing someone's money; hence, financial resources.</defn>
    <defn>An indention and cavity with a net sack or similar structure (into which the balls are to be struck) at each corner and one centered on each side of a pool or snooker table.</defn>
    <defn>An enclosed volume of one substance surrounded by another.</defn>
    <defn>An area of land surrounded by a loop of a river.</defn>
    <defn>The region directly behind the offensive line in which the quarterback executes plays.</defn>
    <defn>An area where military units are completely surrounded by enemy units.</defn>
    <defn>The position held by a second defensive middle, where an advanced middle must retreat after making a touch on the attacking middle.</defn>
    <defn>A hole or space covered by a movable piece of board, as in a floor, boxing, partitions, etc.</defn>
    <defn>A cavity in a rock containing a nugget of gold, or other mineral; a small body of ore contained in such a cavity.</defn>
    <defn>A strip of canvas sewn upon a sail so that a batten or a light spar can placed in the interspace.</defn>
    <defn>The pouch of an animal.</defn>
    <defn>The ideal point where the pins are hit by the bowling ball.</defn>
    <defn>A socket for receiving the base of a post, stake, etc.</defn>
    <defn>A bight on a lee shore.</defn>
    <defn>A small space between a tooth and the adjoining gum, formed by an abnormal separation of the two.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>point</word>
    <defn>A discrete division of something.</defn>
    <defn>A sharp extremity.</defn>
    <defn>One of the several different parts of the escutcheon.</defn>
    <defn>A short piece of cordage used in reefing sails.</defn>
    <defn>A string or lace used to tie together certain garments.</defn>
    <defn>Lace worked by the needle.</defn>
    <defn>The perpendicular rising of a hawk over the place where its prey has gone into cover.</defn>
    <defn>The gesture of extending the index finger in a direction in order to indicate something.</defn>
    <defn>In various sports, a position of a certain player, or, by extension, the player occupying that position.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>pole</word>
    <defn>Originally, a stick; now specifically, a long and slender piece of metal or (especially) wood, used for various construction or support purposes.</defn>
    <defn>A type of basic fishing rod.</defn>
    <defn>(spotting) A telescope used to identify birds, aeroplanes or wildlife.</defn>
    <defn>A unit of length, equal to a rod (1/4 chain or 5 1/2 yards).</defn>
    <defn>Pole position.</defn>
    <defn>A gun.</defn>
    <defn>A penis</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>politician</word>
    <defn>One engaged in politics, especially an elected or appointed government official.</defn>
    <defn>Specifically, one who regards elected political office as a career.</defn>
    <defn>A politically active or interested person.</defn>
    <defn>A sly or ingratiating person.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>politics</word>
    <defn>To engage in political activity; politick.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>poll</word>
    <defn>A survey of people, usually statistically analyzed to gauge wider public opinion.</defn>
    <defn>A formal election.</defn>
    <defn>(now rare outside veterinary medicine contexts) The head, particularly the scalp or pate upon which hair (normally) grows.</defn>
    <defn>(in extended senses of the above) A mass of people, a mob or muster, considered as a head count.</defn>
    <defn>The broad or butt end of an axe or a hammer.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>popular</word>
    <defn>(chiefly in the plural) An inexpensive newspaper with wide circulation.</defn>
    <defn>A member of the Populares</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>positive</word>
    <defn>A thing capable of being affirmed; something real or actual.</defn>
    <defn>A favourable point or characteristic.</defn>
    <defn>(grammar) A degree of comparison of adjectives and adverbs.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>powerful</word>
    <defn>Having, or capable of exerting power, potency or influence.</defn>
    <defn>Large; capacious; said of veins of ore.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>preference</word>
    <defn>The selection of one thing or person over others (with the main adposition being "for" in relation to the thing or person, but possibly also "of")</defn>
    <defn>The option to so select, and the one selected.</defn>
    <defn>The state of being preferred over others.</defn>
    <defn>A strong liking or personal valuation.</defn>
    <defn>A preferential bias; partiality; discrimination.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>preparation</word>
    <defn>The act of preparing or getting ready.</defn>
    <defn>The state of being prepared; readiness.</defn>
    <defn>That which is prepared.</defn>
    <defn>The day before the Sabbath or other Jewish feast-day.</defn>
    <defn>Devotional exercises introducing an office.</defn>
    <defn>The previous introduction, as an integral part of a chord, of a note continued into a succeeding dissonance.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>prescription</word>
    <defn>The act of prescribing a rule, law, etc..</defn>
    <defn>A written order, as by a physician or nurse practitioner, for the administration of a medicine or other intervention. See also scrip.</defn>
    <defn>The formal description of the lens geometry needed for spectacles, etc..</defn>
    <defn>The act or practice of laying down norms of language usage, as opposed to description, i.e. recording and describing actual usage.</defn>
    <defn>An instance of a prescriptive pronouncement.</defn>
    <defn>A plan or procedure to obtain a given end result; a recipe.</defn>
    <defn>Circumscription; restraint; limitation.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>presentation</word>
    <defn>The act of presenting, or something presented</defn>
    <defn>A dramatic performance</defn>
    <defn>An award given to someone on a special occasion</defn>
    <defn>Money given as a wedding gift.</defn>
    <defn>A lecture or speech given in front of an audience</defn>
    <defn>The symptoms and other possible indications of disease, trauma, etc., that are exhibited by a patient who has sought, or has otherwise come to, the attention of a physician, e.g., "Thirty-four-year-old male presented in the emergency room with slight fever, dilated pupils, and marked disorientation."</defn>
    <defn>The position of the foetus in the uterus at birth</defn>
    <defn>Offering one's blade for engagement by the opponent</defn>
    <defn>The specification of a group by generators and relators.</defn>
    <defn>The act or right of offering a clergyman to the bishop or ordinary for institution in a benefice.</defn>
    <defn>The preparation of antigen fragments during the immune response</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>presidential</word>
    <defn>Pertaining to a president or presidency.</defn>
    <defn>Presiding or watching over.</defn>
    <defn>With the bearing or composure that befits a president; stately, dignified.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>print</word>
    <defn>Clear handwriting, especially, writing without connected letters as in cursive.</defn>
    <defn>The letters forming the text of a document.</defn>
    <defn>A newspaper.</defn>
    <defn>A visible impression on a surface.</defn>
    <defn>A copy of a film that can be projected.</defn>
    <defn>A plaster cast in bas relief.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>priority</word>
    <defn>An item's relative importance.</defn>
    <defn>A goal of a person or an organisation.</defn>
    <defn>The quality of being earlier or coming first compared to another thing; the state of being prior.</defn>
    <defn>(of a name) A superior claim to use by virtue of being validly published at an earlier date.</defn>
    <defn>Precedence; superior rank.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>privacy</word>
    <defn>The state of being secluded from the presence, sight, or knowledge of others.</defn>
    <defn>Freedom from unwanted or undue disturbance of one private life.</defn>
    <defn>Freedom from damaging publicity, public scrutiny, surveillance, and disclosure of personal information, usually by a government or a private organization.</defn>
    <defn>A place of seclusion.</defn>
    <defn>A relationship between parties seen as being a result of their mutual interest or participation in a given transaction, contract etc.; Privity.</defn>
    <defn>Secrecy.</defn>
    <defn>A private matter; a secret.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>procedure</word>
    <defn>A particular method for performing a task.</defn>
    <defn>A series of small tasks or steps taken to accomplish an end.</defn>
    <defn>The set of established forms or methods of an organized body for accomplishing a certain task or tasks.</defn>
    <defn>The steps taken in an action or other legal proceeding.</defn>
    <defn>That which results; issue; product.</defn>
    <defn>A subroutine or function coded to perform a specific task.</defn>
    <defn>A surgical operation.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>professor</word>
    <defn>A teacher or faculty member at a college or university regardless of formal rank.</defn>
    <defn>One who professes something, such as a religious doctrine.</defn>
    <defn>A pianist in a saloon, brothel, etc.</defn>
    <defn>The puppeteer who performs a Punch and Judy show; a Punchman.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>profile</word>
    <defn>The outermost shape, view, or edge of an object.</defn>
    <defn>The shape, view, or shadow of a person's head from the side; a side view.</defn>
    <defn>A summary or collection of information, especially about a person</defn>
    <defn>A specific space or field in which users can provide various types of personal information in software or Internet systems.</defn>
    <defn>Reputation.</defn>
    <defn>The amount by which something protrudes.</defn>
    <defn>Prominence; noticeability.</defn>
    <defn>A smoothed (e.g., troweled or brushed) vertical surface of an excavation showing evidence of at least one feature or diagnostic specimen; the graphic recording of such as by sketching, photographing, etc.</defn>
    <defn>Character; totality of related characteristics; signature; status (especially in scientific, technical, or military uses).</defn>
    <defn>A section of any member, made at right angles with its main lines, showing the exact shape of mouldings etc.</defn>
    <defn>A drawing exhibiting a vertical section of the ground along a surveyed line, or graded work, as of a railway, showing elevations, depressions, grades, etc.</defn>
    <defn>An exemption from certain types of duties due to injury or disability.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>prominent</word>
    <defn>Standing out, or projecting; jutting; protuberant</defn>
    <defn>Likely to attract attention from its size or position; conspicuous</defn>
    <defn>Eminent; distinguished above others</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>prompt</word>
    <defn>A reminder or cue.</defn>
    <defn>A time limit given for payment of an account for produce purchased, this limit varying with different goods.</defn>
    <defn>A sequence of characters that appears on a monitor to indicate that the computer is ready to receive input.</defn>
    <defn>(writing) A suggestion for inspiration given to an author.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>proud</word>
    <defn>Feeling honoured (by something); feeling happy or satisfied about an event or fact; gratified.</defn>
    <defn>Possessed of a due sense of what one deserves or is worth.</defn>
    <defn>Having too high an opinion of oneself; arrogant, supercilious.</defn>
    <defn>Generating a sense of pride; being a cause for pride.</defn>
    <defn>Standing out or raised; swollen.</defn>
    <defn>Brave, valiant; gallant.</defn>
    <defn>Excited by sexual desire; specifically of a female animal: in heat.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>purchase</word>
    <defn>The acquisition of title to, or property in, anything for a price; buying for money or its equivalent.</defn>
    <defn>That which is obtained, got or acquired, in any manner, honestly or dishonestly; property; possession; acquisition.</defn>
    <defn>That which is obtained for a price in money or its equivalent.</defn>
    <defn>The act or process of seeking and obtaining something (e.g. property, etc.)</defn>
    <defn>A price paid for a house or estate, etc. equal to the amount of the rent or income during the stated number of years.</defn>
    <defn>Any mechanical hold or advantage, applied to the raising or removing of heavy bodies, as by a lever, a tackle or capstan.</defn>
    <defn>The apparatus, tackle or device by which such mechanical advantage is gained and in nautical terminology the ratio of such a device, like a pulley, or block and tackle.</defn>
    <defn>The amount of hold one has from an individual foothold or ledge.</defn>
    <defn>Acquisition of lands or tenements by means other than descent or inheritance, namely, by one's own act or agreement.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>put</word>
    <defn>A right to sell something at a predetermined price.</defn>
    <defn>A contract to sell a security at a set price on or before a certain date.</defn>
    <defn>An old card game.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>qualify</word>
    <defn>An instance of throwing and catching each prop at least twice.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>quietly</word>
    <defn>In a quiet manner.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>race</word>
    <defn>Swift progress; rapid motion; an instance of moving or driving at high speed.</defn>
    <defn>A progressive movement toward a goal.</defn>
    <defn>A fast-moving current of water, such as that which powers a mill wheel.</defn>
    <defn>A water channel, esp. one built to lead water to or from a point where it is utilised.</defn>
    <defn>Competitive action of any kind, especially when prolonged; hence, career; course of life.</defn>
    <defn>The bushings of a rolling element bearing which contacts the rolling elements.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>rapid</word>
    <defn>(often in the plural) a rough section of a river or stream which is difficult to navigate due to the swift and turbulent motion of the water.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>reaction</word>
    <defn>An action or statement in response to a stimulus or other event.</defn>
    <defn>A transformation in which one or more substances is converted into another by combination or decomposition.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>reader</word>
    <defn>A person who reads</defn>
    <defn>A person who reads a publication.</defn>
    <defn>A person who recites literary works, usually to an audience.</defn>
    <defn>A person employed by a publisher to read works submitted for publication and determine their merits</defn>
    <defn>A university lecturer ranking below a professor.</defn>
    <defn>Any device that reads something.</defn>
    <defn>A book of exercises to accompany a textbook.</defn>
    <defn>An elementary textbook for those learning to read, especially for foreign languages.</defn>
    <defn>A literary anthology.</defn>
    <defn>A lay or minor cleric who reads lessons in a church service.</defn>
    <defn>A newspaper advertisement designed to look like a news article rather than a commercial solicitation.</defn>
    <defn>(in the plural) Reading glasses.</defn>
    <defn>(in the plural) Marked playing cards used by cheats.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>really</word>
    <defn>In a way or manner that is real, not unreal.</defn>
    <defn>(modal) Actually; in fact; in reality.</defn>
    <defn>(as an intensifier) Very (modifying an adjective); very much (modifying a verb).</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>recognition</word>
    <defn>The act of recognizing or the condition of being recognized (matching a current observation with a memory of a prior observation of the same entity)</defn>
    <defn>Acceptance as valid or true</defn>
    <defn>Official acceptance of the status of a new government by that of another country</defn>
    <defn>Honour, favourable note, or attention</defn>
    <defn>The propriety consisting for antibodies to bind to some specific antigens and not to others.</defn>
    <defn>A return of the feu to the superior.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>recording</word>
    <defn>To make a record of information.</defn>
    <defn>To give legal status to by making an official public record.</defn>
    <defn>To fix in a medium, usually in a tangible medium.</defn>
    <defn>To repeat; to practice.</defn>
    <defn>To sing or repeat a tune.</defn>
    <defn>To reflect; to ponder.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>recover</word>
    <defn>Recovery.</defn>
    <defn>A position of holding a firearm during exercises, whereby the lock is at shoulder height and the sling facing out.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>recruit</word>
    <defn>A supply of anything wasted or exhausted; a reinforcement.</defn>
    <defn>A person enlisted for service in the army; a newly enlisted soldier.</defn>
    <defn>A hired worker</defn>
    <defn>A new member of a certain population, usually a juvenile.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>reference</word>
    <defn>A relationship or relation (to something).</defn>
    <defn>A measurement one can compare to.</defn>
    <defn>Information about a person, provided by someone (a referee) with whom they are well acquainted.</defn>
    <defn>A person who provides this information; a referee.</defn>
    <defn>The act of referring: a submitting for information or decision.</defn>
    <defn>A relation between objects in which one object designates, or acts as a means by which to connect to or link to, another object.</defn>
    <defn>(academic writing) A short written identification of a previously published work which is used as a source for a text.</defn>
    <defn>(academic writing) A previously published written work thus indicated; a source.</defn>
    <defn>An object containing information which refers to data stored elsewhere, as opposed to containing the data itself.</defn>
    <defn>(character entity) A special sequence used to represent complex characters in markup languages, such as &#8482; for the &#8482; symbol.</defn>
    <defn>Appeal.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>regard</word>
    <defn>A steady look, a gaze.</defn>
    <defn>One's concern for another; esteem; relation, reference.</defn>
    <defn>(preceded by &#8220;in&#8221; or &#8220;with&#8221;) A particular aspect or detail; respect, sense.</defn>
    <defn>The worth or estimation in which something or someone is held.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>regime</word>
    <defn>Mode of rule or management.</defn>
    <defn>A form of government, or the government in power.</defn>
    <defn>A period of rule.</defn>
    <defn>A set of characteristics.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>region</word>
    <defn>Any considerable and connected part of a space or surface; specifically, a tract of land or sea of considerable but indefinite extent; a country; a district; in a broad sense, a place without special reference to location or extent but viewed as an entity for geographical, social or cultural reasons.</defn>
    <defn>An administrative subdivision of a city, a territory, a country.</defn>
    <defn>A place in or a part of the body in any way indicated.</defn>
    <defn>Place; rank; station; dignity.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>reject</word>
    <defn>An unpopular person.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>relate</word>
    <defn>To tell in a descriptive way.</defn>
    <defn>To bring into a relation, association, or connection (between one thing and another).</defn>
    <defn>To have a connection.</defn>
    <defn>To interact.</defn>
    <defn>To respond through reaction.</defn>
    <defn>(with to) To identify with; to understand.</defn>
    <defn>To bring back; to restore.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>relationship</word>
    <defn>Connection or association; the condition of being related.</defn>
    <defn>The links between the x-values and y-values of ordered pairs of numbers especially coordinates.</defn>
    <defn>Kinship; being related by blood or marriage.</defn>
    <defn>A romantic or sexual involvement.</defn>
    <defn>A way in which two or more people behave and are involved with each other</defn>
    <defn>The level or degree of affinity between keys, chords and tones.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>rely</word>
    <defn>(with on or upon, formerly also with in) to trust; to have confidence in; to depend.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>remote</word>
    <defn>An element of broadcast programming originating away from the station's or show's control room.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>repeat</word>
    <defn>An iteration; a repetition.</defn>
    <defn>A television program shown after its initial presentation; a rerun.</defn>
    <defn>A refill of a prescription.</defn>
    <defn>A pattern of nucleic acids that occur in multiple copies throughout a genome (or of amino acids in a protein).</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>representative</word>
    <defn>A delegate.</defn>
    <defn>Something standing for something else.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>respondent</word>
    <defn>One who responds; one who replies.</defn>
    <defn>A defendant, especially in a case instituted by a petition or in appellate and divorce proceedings.</defn>
    <defn>A person replying to a questionnaire.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>restore</word>
    <defn>The act of recovering data or a system from a backup.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>retire</word>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>revenue</word>
    <defn>The income returned by an investment.</defn>
    <defn>The total income received from a given source.</defn>
    <defn>All income generated for some political entity's treasury by taxation and other means.</defn>
    <defn>The total sales; turnover.</defn>
    <defn>The net income from normal business operations; net sales.</defn>
    <defn>A return; something paid back.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>rice</word>
    <defn>Cereal plants, Oryza sativa of the grass family whose seeds are used as food.</defn>
    <defn>A specific variety of this plant.</defn>
    <defn>The seeds of this plant used as food.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>rich</word>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>root</word>
    <defn>The part of a plant, generally underground, that anchors and supports the plant body, absorbs and stores water and nutrients, and in some plants is able to perform vegetative reproduction.</defn>
    <defn>The part of a tooth extending into the bone holding the tooth in place.</defn>
    <defn>The part of a hair under the skin that holds the hair in place.</defn>
    <defn>The part of a hair near the skin that has not been dyed, permed, or otherwise treated.</defn>
    <defn>The primary source; origin.</defn>
    <defn>Of a number or expression, a number which, when raised to a specified power, yields the specified number or expression.</defn>
    <defn>A zero (of an equation).</defn>
    <defn>The single node of a tree that has no parent.</defn>
    <defn>(philology) A word from which another word or words are derived.</defn>
    <defn>The fundamental tone of any chord; the tone from whose harmonics, or overtones, a chord is composed.</defn>
    <defn>The lowest place, position, or part.</defn>
    <defn>The highest directory of a directory structure which may contain both files and subdirectories.</defn>
    <defn>A penis, especially the base of a penis.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>row</word>
    <defn>A line of objects, often regularly spaced, such as seats in a theatre, vegetable plants in a garden etc.</defn>
    <defn>A line of entries in a table, etc., going from left to right, as opposed to a column going from top to bottom.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>rule</word>
    <defn>A regulation, law, guideline.</defn>
    <defn>A straight line (continuous mark, as made by a pen or the like), especially one lying across a paper as a guide for writing.</defn>
    <defn>A regulating principle.</defn>
    <defn>The act of ruling; administration of law; government; empire; authority; control.</defn>
    <defn>A normal condition or state of affairs.</defn>
    <defn>Conduct; behaviour.</defn>
    <defn>An order regulating the practice of the courts, or an order made between parties to an action or a suit.</defn>
    <defn>A determinate method prescribed for performing any operation and producing a certain result.</defn>
    <defn>A thin plate of brass or other metal, of the same height as the type, and used for printing lines, as between columns on the same page, or in tabular work.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>salary</word>
    <defn>A fixed amount of money paid to a worker, usually calculated on a monthly or annual basis, not hourly, as wages. Implies a degree of professionalism and/or autonomy.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>sanction</word>
    <defn>An approval, by an authority, generally one that makes something valid.</defn>
    <defn>A penalty, punishment, or some coercive measure, intended to ensure compliance; especially one adopted by several nations, or by an international body.</defn>
    <defn>A law, treaty, or contract, or a clause within a law, treaty, or contract, specifying any of the above.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>science</word>
    <defn>A particular discipline or branch of learning, especially one dealing with measurable or systematic principles rather than intuition or natural ability.</defn>
    <defn>Knowledge gained through study or practice; mastery of a particular discipline or area.</defn>
    <defn>The fact of knowing something; knowledge or understanding of a truth.</defn>
    <defn>The collective discipline of study or learning acquired through the scientific method; the sum of knowledge gained from such methods and discipline.</defn>
    <defn>Knowledge derived from scientific disciplines, scientific method, or any systematic effort.</defn>
    <defn>(collective) The scientific community.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>sector</word>
    <defn>Section</defn>
    <defn>Zone (designated area).</defn>
    <defn>Part of a circle, extending to the center</defn>
    <defn>Fixed-sized unit (traditionally 512 bytes) of sequential data stored on a track of a digital medium (compare to block)</defn>
    <defn>An area designated by boundaries within which a unit operates, and for which it is responsible</defn>
    <defn>One of the subdivisions of a coastal frontier</defn>
    <defn>A fictional region of space designated for navigational or governance purposes.</defn>
    <defn>(calculation) an instrument consisting of two rulers of equal length joined by a hinge.</defn>
    <defn>A field of economic activity</defn>
    <defn>A toothed gear whose face is the arc of a circle.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>select</word>
    <defn>To choose one or more elements of a set, especially a set of options.</defn>
    <defn>To obtain a set of data from a database using a query.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>sequence</word>
    <defn>A set of things next to each other in a set order; a series</defn>
    <defn>The state of being sequent or following; order of succession.</defn>
    <defn>A series of musical phrases where a theme or melody is repeated, with some change each time, such as in pitch or length (example: opening of Beethoven's Fifth Symphony).</defn>
    <defn>An ordered list of objects, typically indexed with natural numbers.</defn>
    <defn>A series of shots that depict a single action or style in a film, television show etc.</defn>
    <defn>A meld consisting of three or more cards of successive ranks in the same suit, such as the four, five and six of hearts.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>seriously</word>
    <defn>(manner) In a serious or literal manner.</defn>
    <defn>Gravely; deeply; very much.</defn>
    <defn>Used to attempt to introduce a serious point in a less serious conversation</defn>
    <defn>Used to call back to a previous point, either in disbelief or emphasis</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>sex</word>
    <defn>The members of such a category, taken collectively.</defn>
    <defn>The distinction and relation between these categories, especially in humans; gender.</defn>
    <defn>Genitalia: a penis or vagina.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>sharp</word>
    <defn>The symbol &#9839;, placed after the name of a note in the key signature or before a note on the staff to indicate that the note is to be played a semitone higher.</defn>
    <defn>A note that is played a semitone higher than usual; denoted by the name of the note that is followed by the symbol &#9839;.</defn>
    <defn>A dishonest person; a cheater.</defn>
    <defn>Part of a stream where the water runs very rapidly.</defn>
    <defn>A sewing needle with a very slender point, more pointed than a blunt or a between.</defn>
    <defn>(in the plural) Fine particles of husk mixed with coarse particle of flour of cereals; middlings.</defn>
    <defn>An expert.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>shift</word>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>ship</word>
    <defn>A water-borne vessel generally larger than a boat.</defn>
    <defn>A sailing vessel with three or more square-rigged masts.</defn>
    <defn>The third card of the Lenormand deck.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>shoe</word>
    <defn>A protective covering for the foot, with a bottom part composed of thick leather or plastic sole and often a thicker heel, and a softer upper part made of leather or synthetic material. Shoes generally do not extend above the ankle, as opposed to boots, which do.</defn>
    <defn>A device for holding multiple decks of playing cards, allowing more games to be played by reducing the time between shuffles.</defn>
    <defn>The outer cover or tread of a pneumatic tire, especially for an automobile.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>shoot</word>
    <defn>The emerging stem and embryonic leaves of a new plant.</defn>
    <defn>A photography session.</defn>
    <defn>An event that is unscripted or legitimate.</defn>
    <defn>A rush of water; a rapid.</defn>
    <defn>A weft thread shot through the shed by the shuttle; a pick.</defn>
    <defn>A shoat; a young pig.</defn>
    <defn>A vein of ore running in the same general direction as the lode.</defn>
    <defn>An inclined plane, either artificial or natural, down which timber, coal, ore, etc., are caused to slide; a chute.</defn>
    <defn>The act of taking all point cards in one hand.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>should</word>
    <defn>(modal, auxiliary verb, defective) Used before a verb to indicate the simple future tense in the first person singular or plural.</defn>
    <defn>Used similarly to indicate determination or obligation in the second and third persons singular or plural.</defn>
    <defn>Used in questions with the first person singular or plural to suggest a possible future action.</defn>
    <defn>To owe.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>shout</word>
    <defn>A loud burst of voice or voices; a violent and sudden outcry, especially that of a multitude expressing joy, triumph, exultation, anger, or animated courage.</defn>
    <defn>A round of drinks in a pub; the turn to pay the shot or scot; an act of paying for a round of drinks.</defn>
    <defn>A call-out for an emergency services team.</defn>
    <defn>A greeting, name-check or other mention, for example on a radio or TV programme.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>shower</word>
    <defn>A brief fall of precipitation (spell of rain, or a similar fall of snow, sleet, or cascade).</defn>
    <defn>A device for bathing by which water is made to fall on the body from a height, either from a tank or by the action of a pump.</defn>
    <defn>An instance of using of this device in order to bathe oneself.</defn>
    <defn>A party associated with a significant event in a person's life, at which the person usually receives gifts.</defn>
    <defn>A battle, an attack; conflict.</defn>
    <defn>(with of and an invective) Used as an intensifying pluralizer or intensifier</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>silence</word>
    <defn>The absence of any sound.</defn>
    <defn>The act of refraining from speaking.</defn>
    <defn>Form of meditative worship practiced by the Society of Friends (Quakers); meeting for worship.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>silver</word>
    <defn>A lustrous, white, metallic element, atomic number 47, atomic weight 107.87, symbol Ag.</defn>
    <defn>A shiny gray color.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>similarly</word>
    <defn>(manner) In a like style or manner.</defn>
    <defn>Used to link similar items</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>sing</word>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>size</word>
    <defn>A regulation determining the amount of money paid in fees, taxes etc.</defn>
    <defn>A fixed standard for the magnitude, quality, quantity etc. of goods, especially food and drink.</defn>
    <defn>The dimensions or magnitude of a thing; how big something is.</defn>
    <defn>A regulation, piece of ordinance.</defn>
    <defn>A specific set of dimensions for a manufactured article, especially clothing.</defn>
    <defn>A number of edges in a graph.</defn>
    <defn>Degree of rank, ability, character, etc.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>slight</word>
    <defn>Sleight.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>slow</word>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>smart</word>
    <defn>To hurt or sting.</defn>
    <defn>To feel a pungent pain of mind; to feel sharp pain or grief; be punished severely; to feel the sting of evil.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>snap</word>
    <defn>A quick breaking or cracking sound or the action of producing such a sound.</defn>
    <defn>A sudden break.</defn>
    <defn>An attempt to seize, bite, attack, or grab.</defn>
    <defn>The sudden release of something held under pressure or tension.</defn>
    <defn>A thin circular cookie or similar baked good.</defn>
    <defn>A backward pass or handoff of a football from its position on the ground that puts the ball in play; a hike.</defn>
    <defn>(somewhat colloquial) A rivet: a scrapbooking embellishment.</defn>
    <defn>A small meal, a snack; lunch.</defn>
    <defn>A greedy fellow.</defn>
    <defn>Briskness; vigour; energy; decision</defn>
    <defn>Something that is easy or effortless.</defn>
    <defn>Jounce (the fourth derivative of the position vector with respect to time), followed by crackle and pop</defn>
    <defn>Something of no value.</defn>
    <defn>A visual message sent through the Snapchat application.</defn>
    <defn>A crisp or pithy quality; epigrammatic point or force.</defn>
    <defn>A tool used by riveters.</defn>
    <defn>A tool used by glass-moulders.</defn>
    <defn>A brief theatrical engagement.</defn>
    <defn>An easy and profitable place or task; a sinecure.</defn>
    <defn>A cheat or sharper.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>soccer</word>
    <defn>Association football</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>society</word>
    <defn>A long-standing group of people sharing cultural aspects such as language, dress, norms of behavior and artistic forms.</defn>
    <defn>A group of people who meet from time to time to engage in a common interest; an association or organization.</defn>
    <defn>The sum total of all voluntary interrelations between individuals.</defn>
    <defn>The people of one&#8217;s country or community taken as a whole.</defn>
    <defn>A number of people joined by mutual consent to deliberate, determine and act toward a common goal.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>soft</word>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>software</word>
    <defn>Encoded computer instructions, usually modifiable (unless stored in some form of unalterable memory such as ROM).</defn>
    <defn>The human beings involved in warfare, as opposed to hardware such as weapons and vehicles.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>soil</word>
    <defn>A mixture of mineral particles and organic material, used to support plant growth.</defn>
    <defn>The unconsolidated mineral or organic material on the immediate surface of the earth that serves as a natural medium for the growth of land plants.</defn>
    <defn>Country or territory.</defn>
    <defn>A marshy or miry place to which a hunted boar resorts for refuge; hence, a wet place, stream, or tract of water, sought for by other game, as deer.</defn>
    <defn>Dung; compost; manure.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>some</word>
    <defn>Of a measurement: approximately, roughly.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>speaker</word>
    <defn>One who speaks.</defn>
    <defn>Speakerphone.</defn>
    <defn>The chair or presiding officer of certain legislative bodies, such as the U.K. House of Commons or the U.S. House of Representatives.</defn>
    <defn>One who makes a speech to an audience.</defn>
    <defn>A book containing passages of text for use in speeches.</defn>
    <defn>The producer of a given utterance (text, etc), whether actually spoken or e.g. written.</defn>
    <defn>A key on a woodwind instrument of the clarinet family (cf octave key on other instruments) which induces the instrument to overblow.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>species</word>
    <defn>Type or kind. (Compare race.)</defn>
    <defn>An image, an appearance, a spectacle.</defn>
    <defn>Either of the two elements of the Eucharist after they have been consecrated.</defn>
    <defn>Coin, or coined silver, gold, or other metal, used as a circulating medium; specie.</defn>
    <defn>A component part of compound medicine; a simple.</defn>
    <defn>An officinal mixture or compound powder of any kind; especially, one used for making an aromatic tea or tisane; a tea mixture.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>specifically</word>
    <defn>In a specific manner, applying to or naming a particular thing or things, expressly, explicitly</defn>
    <defn>For a specific purpose or reason</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>spend</word>
    <defn>Amount of money spent (during a period); expenditure.</defn>
    <defn>(in the plural) Expenditures; money or pocket money.</defn>
    <defn>Discharged semen.</defn>
    <defn>Vaginal discharge.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>split</word>
    <defn>A crack or longitudinal fissure.</defn>
    <defn>A breach or separation, as in a political party; a division.</defn>
    <defn>(leather manufacture) One of the sections of a skin made by dividing it into two or more thicknesses.</defn>
    <defn>A workout routine as seen by its distribution of muscle groups or the extent and manner they are targetted in a microcycle.</defn>
    <defn>A result of a first throw that leaves two or more pins standing with one or more pins between them knocked down.</defn>
    <defn>A unit of measure used for champagne or other spirits: 18.75 centiliters or one quarter of a standard 75-centiliter bottle. Commercially comparable to 1/20 gallon, which is 1/2 of a fifth.</defn>
    <defn>A bottle of wine containing 37.5 centiliters, half the volume of a standard 75-centiliter bottle; a demi.</defn>
    <defn>The elapsed time at specific intermediate points in a race.</defn>
    <defn>The elapsed time at specific intermediate points in a speedrun.</defn>
    <defn>A tear resulting from tensile stresses.</defn>
    <defn>A division of a stake happening when two cards of the kind on which the stake is laid are dealt in the same turn.</defn>
    <defn>A recording containing songs by multiple artists.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>spokesman</word>
    <defn>One who speaks as the voice of a group of people.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>sport</word>
    <defn>Any activity that uses physical exertion or skills competitively under a set of rules that is not based on aesthetics.</defn>
    <defn>Something done for fun, regardless of its design or intended purpose.</defn>
    <defn>That which diverts, and makes mirth; pastime; amusement.</defn>
    <defn>Mockery, making fun; derision.</defn>
    <defn>A toy; a plaything; an object of mockery.</defn>
    <defn>Gaming for money as in racing, hunting, fishing.</defn>
    <defn>A plant or an animal, or part of a plant or animal, which has some peculiarity not usually seen in the species; an abnormal variety or growth. The term encompasses both mutants and organisms with non-genetic developmental abnormalities such as birth defects.</defn>
    <defn>One who consorts with disreputable people, including prostitutes.</defn>
    <defn>An amorous dalliance.</defn>
    <defn>(usually singular) A friend or acquaintance (chiefly used when speaking to the friend in question)</defn>
    <defn>Play; idle jingle.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>spring</word>
    <defn>To weaken, as a joint, ligament, or muscle, by sudden and excessive exertion, as by wrenching; to overstrain, or stretch injuriously, but without luxation</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>stable</word>
    <defn>A building, wing or dependency set apart and adapted for lodging and feeding (and training) animals with hoofs, especially horses.</defn>
    <defn>A set of advocates; a barristers' chambers.</defn>
    <defn>An organization of sumo wrestlers who live and train together.</defn>
    <defn>A group of prostitutes managed by one pimp.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>start</word>
    <defn>The beginning of an activity.</defn>
    <defn>A sudden involuntary movement.</defn>
    <defn>The beginning point of a race, a board game, etc.</defn>
    <defn>An appearance in a sports game, horserace, etc., from the beginning of the event.</defn>
    <defn>A young plant germinated in a pot to be transplanted later.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>station</word>
    <defn>A stopping place.</defn>
    <defn>Any of the Stations of the Cross.</defn>
    <defn>The Roman Catholic fast of the fourth and sixth days of the week, Wednesday and Friday, in memory of the council which condemned Christ, and of his passion.</defn>
    <defn>A church in which the procession of the clergy halts on stated days to say stated prayers.</defn>
    <defn>Standing; rank; position.</defn>
    <defn>A broadcasting entity.</defn>
    <defn>A harbour or cove with a foreshore suitable for a facility to support nearby fishing.</defn>
    <defn>Any of a sequence of equally spaced points along a path.</defn>
    <defn>The particular place, or kind of situation, in which a species naturally occurs; a habitat.</defn>
    <defn>An enlargement in a shaft or galley, used as a landing, or passing place, or for the accommodation of a pump, tank, etc.</defn>
    <defn>Post assigned; office; the part or department of public duty which a person is appointed to perform; sphere of duty or occupation; employment.</defn>
    <defn>The position of the foetal head in relation to the distance from the ischial spines, measured in centimetres.</defn>
    <defn>The fact of standing still; motionlessness, stasis.</defn>
    <defn>The apparent standing still of a superior planet just before it begins or ends its retrograde motion.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>stir</word>
    <defn>Agitation; tumult; bustle; noise or various movements.</defn>
    <defn>Public disturbance or commotion; tumultuous disorder; seditious uproar.</defn>
    <defn>Agitation of thoughts; conflicting passions.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>story</word>
    <defn>A sequence of real or fictional events; or, an account of such a sequence.</defn>
    <defn>A lie, fiction.</defn>
    <defn>(usually pluralized) A soap opera.</defn>
    <defn>A sequence of events, or a situation, such as might be related in an account.</defn>
    <defn>A chronological collection of pictures or short videos published by a user on an application or website that is typically only available for a short period.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>style</word>
    <defn>Senses relating to a thin, pointed object.</defn>
    <defn>(by extension from sense 1.1) A particular manner of expression in writing or speech, especially one regarded as good.</defn>
    <defn>A particular manner of creating, doing, or presenting something, especially a work of architecture or art.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>substantial</word>
    <defn>Anything having substance; an essential part.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>sue</word>
    <defn>To file a legal action against someone, generally a non-criminal action.</defn>
    <defn>To seek by request; to make application; to petition; to entreat; to plead.</defn>
    <defn>(of a hawk) To clean (the beak, etc.).</defn>
    <defn>To leave high and dry on shore.</defn>
    <defn>To court.</defn>
    <defn>To follow.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>sufficient</word>
    <defn>Equal to the end proposed; adequate to what is needed; enough</defn>
    <defn>Possessing adequate talents or accomplishments; of competent power or ability; qualified; fit.</defn>
    <defn>Capable of meeting obligations; responsible.</defn>
    <defn>Having enough money to meet obligations and live comfortably.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>suggest</word>
    <defn>To imply but stop short of saying explicitly.</defn>
    <defn>To make one suppose; cause one to suppose (something).</defn>
    <defn>To mention something as an idea, typically in order to recommend it</defn>
    <defn>To seduce; to prompt to evil; to tempt.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>surface</word>
    <defn>The overside or up-side of a flat object such as a table, or of a liquid.</defn>
    <defn>The outside hull of a tangible object.</defn>
    <defn>Outward or external appearance.</defn>
    <defn>The locus of an equation (especially one with exactly two degrees of freedom) in a more-than-two-dimensional space.</defn>
    <defn>(fortification) That part of the side which is terminated by the flank prolonged, and the angle of the nearest bastion.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>surprised</word>
    <defn>To cause (someone) to feel unusually alarmed or delighted by something unexpected.</defn>
    <defn>To do something to (a person) that they are not expecting, as a surprise.</defn>
    <defn>To undergo or witness something unexpected.</defn>
    <defn>To cause surprise.</defn>
    <defn>To attack unexpectedly.</defn>
    <defn>To take unawares.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>surprisingly</word>
    <defn>In a way that causes surprise because it is unexpected, or unusual.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>switch</word>
    <defn>A bundle of thin sticks, typically made of wood, sometimes bond in such a way that binding can be moved so that it varies the tightness of the binding.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>tablespoon</word>
    <defn>A large spoon, used for eating food from a bowl.</defn>
    <defn>A spoon too large for eating, usually used for cooking or serving.</defn>
    <defn>A unit of volume, the value of which varies regionally; in the US: three teaspoons or roughly 15 ml; in Britain and Canada: exactly 15 ml; in Australia: four teaspoons or 20 ml.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>take</word>
    <defn>The or an act of taking.</defn>
    <defn>An interpretation or view, opinion or assessment; perspective.</defn>
    <defn>An approach, a (distinct) treatment.</defn>
    <defn>A scene recorded (filmed) at one time, without an interruption or break; a recording of such a scene.</defn>
    <defn>A recording of a musical performance made during an uninterrupted single recording period.</defn>
    <defn>A visible (facial) response to something, especially something unexpected; a facial gesture in response to an event.</defn>
    <defn>An instance of successful inoculation/vaccination.</defn>
    <defn>A catch of the ball (in cricket, especially one by the wicket-keeper).</defn>
    <defn>The quantity of copy given to a compositor at one time.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>tax</word>
    <defn>Money paid to the government other than for transaction-specific goods and services.</defn>
    <defn>A burdensome demand.</defn>
    <defn>A task exacted from one who is under control; a contribution or service, the rendering of which is imposed upon a subject.</defn>
    <defn>Charge; censure</defn>
    <defn>A lesson to be learned.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>tear</word>
    <defn>A rampage.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>technology</word>
    <defn>The organization of knowledge for practical purposes.</defn>
    <defn>All the different and usable technologies developed by a culture or people.</defn>
    <defn>A discourse or treatise on the arts.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>telephone</word>
    <defn>A telecommunication device (originally mechanical, and now electronic) used for two-way talking with another person (now often shortened to phone).</defn>
    <defn>The game of Chinese whispers.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>ten</word>
    <defn>A perfect specimen, a physically attractive person.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>terror</word>
    <defn>Intense dread, fright, or fear.</defn>
    <defn>The action or quality of causing dread; terribleness, especially such qualities in narrative fiction.</defn>
    <defn>Something or someone that causes such fear.</defn>
    <defn>Terrorism</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>them</word>
    <defn>(plural) Those ones.</defn>
    <defn>(singular) Him, her, or it; that one.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>therapy</word>
    <defn>Attempted remediation of a health problem following a diagnosis, usually synonymous with treatment.</defn>
    <defn>Healing power or quality.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>thin</word>
    <defn>A loss or tearing of paper from the back of a stamp, although not sufficient to create a complete hole.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>thing</word>
    <defn>That which is considered to exist as a separate entity, object, quality or concept.</defn>
    <defn>A word, symbol, sign, or other referent that can be used to refer to any entity.</defn>
    <defn>An individual object or distinct entity.</defn>
    <defn>Whatever can be owned.</defn>
    <defn>Corporeal object.</defn>
    <defn>(somewhat obsolete, with the) The latest fad or fashion.</defn>
    <defn>(in the plural) Clothes, possessions or equipment.</defn>
    <defn>A unit or container, usually containing edible goods.</defn>
    <defn>A problem, dilemma, or complicating factor.</defn>
    <defn>A penis.</defn>
    <defn>A living being or creature.</defn>
    <defn>That which matters; the crux.</defn>
    <defn>Used after a noun to refer dismissively to the situation surrounding the noun's referent.</defn>
    <defn>That which is favoured; personal preference. (Used in possessive constructions.)</defn>
    <defn>A public assembly or judicial council in a Germanic country.</defn>
    <defn>A romantic relationship.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>thirty</word>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>time</word>
    <defn>The inevitable progression into the future with the passing of present and past events.</defn>
    <defn>The measurement under some system of region of day or moment.</defn>
    <defn>Ratio of comparison.</defn>
    <defn>(grammar) Tense.</defn>
    <defn>The measured duration of sounds; measure; tempo; rate of movement; rhythmical division.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>tonight</word>
    <defn>The nighttime of the current day or date; this night.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>topic</word>
    <defn>Subject; theme; a category or general area of interest.</defn>
    <defn>Discussion thread.</defn>
    <defn>A musical sign intended to suggest a particular style or genre.</defn>
    <defn>An argument or reason.</defn>
    <defn>An external local application or remedy, such as a plaster, a blister, etc.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>tower</word>
    <defn>A very tall iron-framed structure, usually painted red and white, on which microwave, radio, satellite, or other communication antennas are installed; mast.</defn>
    <defn>A similarly framed structure with a platform or enclosed area on top, used as a lookout for spotting fires, plane crashes, fugitives, etc.</defn>
    <defn>Any very tall building or structure; skyscraper.</defn>
    <defn>Any item, such as a computer case, that is usually higher than it is wide.</defn>
    <defn>A strong refuge; a defence.</defn>
    <defn>A tall fashionable headdress worn in the time of King William III and Queen Anne.</defn>
    <defn>High flight; elevation.</defn>
    <defn>The sixteenth trump or Major Arcana card in many Tarot decks, usually deemed an ill omen.</defn>
    <defn>The nineteenth Lenormand card, representing structure, bureaucracy, stability and loneliness.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>training</word>
    <defn>To practice an ability.</defn>
    <defn>To teach and form (someone) by practice; to educate (someone).</defn>
    <defn>To improve one's fitness.</defn>
    <defn>To proceed in sequence.</defn>
    <defn>To move (a gun) laterally so that it points in a different direction.</defn>
    <defn>To encourage (a plant or branch) to grow in a particular direction or shape, usually by pruning and bending.</defn>
    <defn>To trace (a lode or any mineral appearance) to its head.</defn>
    <defn>To create a trainer for; to apply cheats to (a game).</defn>
    <defn>To draw along; to trail; to drag.</defn>
    <defn>To draw by persuasion, artifice, or the like; to attract by stratagem; to entice; to allure.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>transformation</word>
    <defn>The act of transforming or the state of being transformed.</defn>
    <defn>A marked change in appearance or character, especially one for the better.</defn>
    <defn>The replacement of the variables in an algebraic expression by their values in terms of another set of variables; a mapping of one space onto another or onto itself; a function that changes the position or direction of the axes of a coordinate system.</defn>
    <defn>A rule that systematically converts one syntactic form into another; a sentence derived by such a rule.</defn>
    <defn>The alteration of a bacterial cell caused by the transfer of DNA from another, especially if pathogenic.</defn>
    <defn>Ideologically driven government policy - becoming more conformant with socialist and African nationalist groupthink.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>translate</word>
    <defn>In Euclidean spaces: a set of points obtained by adding a given fixed vector to each point of a given set.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>treat</word>
    <defn>An entertainment, outing, food, drink, or other indulgence provided by someone for the enjoyment of others.</defn>
    <defn>An unexpected gift, event etc., which provides great pleasure.</defn>
    <defn>A snack food item designed to be given to pets.</defn>
    <defn>A parley or discussion of terms; a negotiation.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>treaty</word>
    <defn>A binding agreement concluded by subjects of international law, namely states and international organizations.</defn>
    <defn>A formal agreement between two or more states.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>trial</word>
    <defn>An opportunity to test something out; a test.</defn>
    <defn>Appearance at judicial court in order to be examined.</defn>
    <defn>A difficult or annoying experience.</defn>
    <defn>A tryout to pick members of a team.</defn>
    <defn>A piece of ware used to test the heat of a kiln.</defn>
    <defn>An internal examination set by Eton College.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>troop</word>
    <defn>(collective) A collection of people; a number; a multitude (in general).</defn>
    <defn>A small unit of cavalry or armour commanded by a captain, corresponding to a platoon or company of infantry.</defn>
    <defn>A company of stageplayers; a troupe.</defn>
    <defn>A basic unit of girl or boy scouts, consisting of 6 to 10 youngsters.</defn>
    <defn>(collective) A group of baboons.</defn>
    <defn>A particular roll of the drum; a quick march.</defn>
    <defn>Mushrooms that are in a close group but not close enough to be called a cluster.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>truck</word>
    <defn>A small wheel or roller, specifically the wheel of a gun carriage.</defn>
    <defn>The ball on top of a flagpole.</defn>
    <defn>A semi-tractor ("semi") trailer; a lorry.</defn>
    <defn>Any motor vehicle designed for carrying cargo, including delivery vans, pickups, and other motorized vehicles (including passenger autos) fitted with a bed designed to carry goods.</defn>
    <defn>A garden cart, a two-wheeled wheelbarrow.</defn>
    <defn>A small wagon or cart, of various designs, pushed or pulled by hand or pulled by an animal, as with those in hotels for moving luggage, or in libraries for transporting books.</defn>
    <defn>A pantechnicon (removal van).</defn>
    <defn>A flatbed railway car; a flatcar.</defn>
    <defn>A pivoting frame, one attached to the bottom of the bed of a railway car at each end, that rests on the axle and which swivels to allow the axle (at each end of which is a solid wheel) to turn with curves in the track; a bogie.</defn>
    <defn>The part of a skateboard or roller skate that joins the wheels to the deck, consisting of a hanger, baseplate, kingpin, and bushings, and sometimes mounted with a riser in between.</defn>
    <defn>A platform with wheels or casters.</defn>
    <defn>Dirt or other messiness.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>turn</word>
    <defn>(heading) to make a non-linear physical movement.</defn>
    <defn>(heading) To change condition or attitude.</defn>
    <defn>To change one's course of action; to take a new approach.</defn>
    <defn>(usually with over) To complete.</defn>
    <defn>Of a player, to go past an opposition player with the ball in one's control.</defn>
    <defn>To bring down the feet of a child in the womb, in order to facilitate delivery.</defn>
    <defn>To invert a type of the same thickness, as a temporary substitute for any sort which is exhausted.</defn>
    <defn>To translate.</defn>
    <defn>To magically or divinely attack undead.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>type</word>
    <defn>A grouping based on shared characteristics; a class.</defn>
    <defn>An individual considered typical of its class, one regarded as typifying a certain profession, environment, etc.</defn>
    <defn>An individual that represents the ideal for its class; an embodiment.</defn>
    <defn>A letter or character used for printing, historically a cast or engraved block.</defn>
    <defn>Something, often a specimen, selected as an objective anchor to connect a scientific name to a taxon; this need not be representative or typical.</defn>
    <defn>Preferred sort of person; sort of person that one is attracted to.</defn>
    <defn>A blood group.</defn>
    <defn>(corpus linguistics) A word that occurs in a text or corpus irrespective of how many times it occurs, as opposed to a token.</defn>
    <defn>An event or person that prefigures or foreshadows a later event - commonly an Old Testament event linked to Christian times.</defn>
    <defn>The original object, or class of objects, scene, face, or conception, which becomes the subject of a copy; especially, the design on the face of a medal or a coin.</defn>
    <defn>A simple compound, used as a mode or pattern to which other compounds are conveniently regarded as being related, and from which they may be actually or theoretically derived.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>understand</word>
    <defn>To grasp a concept fully and thoroughly, especially (of words, statements, art, etc.) to be aware of the meaning of and (of people) to be aware of the intent of.</defn>
    <defn>To believe, to think one grasps sufficiently despite potentially incomplete knowledge.</defn>
    <defn>(obsolete outside circus, acrobatics) To stand underneath, to support.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>union</word>
    <defn>The act of uniting or joining two or more things into one.</defn>
    <defn>The state of being united or joined; a state of unity or harmony.</defn>
    <defn>That which is united, or made one; something formed by a combination or coalition of parts or members; a confederation; a consolidated body; a league.</defn>
    <defn>An association of students at a university for social and/or political purposes; also in some cases a debating body.</defn>
    <defn>A joint or other connection uniting parts of machinery, such as pipes.</defn>
    <defn>The set containing all of the elements of two or more sets.</defn>
    <defn>The act or state of marriage.</defn>
    <defn>Sexual intercourse.</defn>
    <defn>A data structure that can store any of various types of item, but only one at a time.</defn>
    <defn>A large, high-quality pearl.</defn>
    <defn>An affiliation of several parishes for joint support and management of their poor; also the jointly-owned workhouse.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>unknown</word>
    <defn>To undo the process of knowing, to lose knowledge of something.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>unless</word>
    <defn>Except on a specified condition; if not.</defn>
    <defn>If not; used with counterfactual conditionals.</defn>
    <defn>Except if; used with hypothetical conditionals.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>unusual</word>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>upper</word>
    <defn>A stimulant, such as amphetamine, that increases energy and decreases appetite.</defn>
    <defn>Someone with higher social standing</defn>
    <defn>That which is higher, contrasted with the lower.</defn>
    <defn>A spiritual passageway through which consciousness can reach a higher dimension.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>useful</word>
    <defn>Having a practical or beneficial use.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>user</word>
    <defn>A person who uses drugs, especially illegal drugs.</defn>
    <defn>In land law, meaning either 1. or 2. above or use. Usually in singular form to mean use wherever there is assiduous re-use of precedents and aloof textbooks verbatim. Modern law, guarded against ambiguity, widely disfavors the term.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>utility</word>
    <defn>The state or condition of being useful; usefulness.</defn>
    <defn>Something that is useful.</defn>
    <defn>The ability of a commodity to satisfy needs or wants; the satisfaction experienced by the consumer of that commodity.</defn>
    <defn>Well-being, satisfaction, pleasure, or happiness.</defn>
    <defn>A service provider, such as an electric company or water company; or, the securities of such a provider.</defn>
    <defn>A software program designed to perform a single task or a small range of tasks, often to help manage and tune computer hardware, an operating system or application software.</defn>
    <defn>The ability to play multiple positions.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>vast</word>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>version</word>
    <defn>A specific form or variation of something.</defn>
    <defn>A translation from one language to another.</defn>
    <defn>A school exercise, generally of composition in a foreign language.</defn>
    <defn>The act of translating, or rendering, from one language into another language.</defn>
    <defn>An account or description from a particular point of view, especially as contrasted with another account.</defn>
    <defn>A particular revision (of software, firmware, CPU, etc.).</defn>
    <defn>An eye movement involving both eyes moving synchronously and symmetrically in the same direction.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>victim</word>
    <defn>One that is harmed&#8212;killed, injured, subjected to oppression, deceived, or otherwise adversely affected&#8212;by someone or something, especially another person or event, force, or condition; in particular:</defn>
    <defn>A living being which is slain and offered as a sacrifice, usually in a religious rite.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>victory</word>
    <defn>An instance of having won a competition or battle or succeeded in an effort.</defn>
    <defn>The condition of having succeeded in a conflict or other effort.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>violation</word>
    <defn>The act or an instance of violating or the condition of being violated.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>violent</word>
    <defn>An assailant.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>virtually</word>
    <defn>Almost but not quite.</defn>
    <defn>Without exaggeration.</defn>
    <defn>In essence, but not in fact.</defn>
    <defn>Of a substructure of finite index.</defn>
    <defn>Of a covering space of finite index.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>visitor</word>
    <defn>Someone who visits someone else; someone staying as a guest.</defn>
    <defn>Someone who pays a visit to a specific place or event; a sightseer or tourist.</defn>
    <defn>(usually in the plural) Someone, or a team, that is playing away from home.</defn>
    <defn>A person authorized to visit an institution to see that it is being managed properly.</defn>
    <defn>An extraterrestrial being on Earth for any reason.</defn>
    <defn>An object which lands or passes by Earth or its orbit.</defn>
    <defn>A head or overseer of an institution such as a college (in which case, equivalent to the university's chancellor) or cathedral or hospital, who resolves disputes, gives ceremonial speeches, etc.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>visual</word>
    <defn>Any element of something that depends on sight.</defn>
    <defn>An image; a picture; a graphic.</defn>
    <defn>A preliminary sketch.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>wall</word>
    <defn>A rampart of earth, stones etc. built up for defensive purposes.</defn>
    <defn>A structure built for defense surrounding a city, castle etc.</defn>
    <defn>Each of the substantial structures acting either as the exterior of or divisions within a structure.</defn>
    <defn>A point of desperation.</defn>
    <defn>A point of defeat or extinction.</defn>
    <defn>An impediment to free movement.</defn>
    <defn>A type of butterfly (Lasiommata megera).</defn>
    <defn>(often in combination) A barrier.</defn>
    <defn>A barrier to vision.</defn>
    <defn>A divisive or containing structure in an organ or cavity.</defn>
    <defn>(auction) A fictional bidder used to increase the price at an auction.</defn>
    <defn>A doctor who tries to admit as few patients as possible.</defn>
    <defn>A line of defenders set up between an opposing free-kick taker and the goal.</defn>
    <defn>A personal notice board listing messages of interest to a particular user.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>watch</word>
    <defn>A portable or wearable timepiece.</defn>
    <defn>The act of guarding and observing someone or something.</defn>
    <defn>A particular time period when guarding is kept.</defn>
    <defn>A person or group of people who guard.</defn>
    <defn>The act of seeing, or viewing, for a period of time.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>weak</word>
    <defn>Lacking in force (usually strength) or ability.</defn>
    <defn>Unable to sustain a great weight, pressure, or strain.</defn>
    <defn>Unable to withstand temptation, urgency, persuasion, etc.; easily impressed, moved, or overcome; accessible; vulnerable.</defn>
    <defn>Dilute, lacking in taste or potency.</defn>
    <defn>(grammar) Displaying a particular kind of inflection, including:</defn>
    <defn>That does not ionize completely into anions and cations in a solution.</defn>
    <defn>One of the four fundamental forces associated with nuclear decay.</defn>
    <defn>Bad or uncool.</defn>
    <defn>Having a narrow range of logical consequences; narrowly applicable. (Often contrasted with a strong statement which implies it.)</defn>
    <defn>Resulting from, or indicating, lack of judgment, discernment, or firmness; unwise; hence, foolish.</defn>
    <defn>Not having power to convince; not supported by force of reason or truth; unsustained.</defn>
    <defn>Lacking in vigour or expression.</defn>
    <defn>Not prevalent or effective, or not felt to be prevalent; not potent; feeble.</defn>
    <defn>Tending towards lower prices.</defn>
    <defn>Lacking contrast.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>weapon</word>
    <defn>An instrument of attack or defense in combat or hunting, e.g. most guns, missiles, or swords.</defn>
    <defn>An instrument or other means of harming or exerting control over another.</defn>
    <defn>A tool of any kind.</defn>
    <defn>An idiot, an oaf, a fool, a tool; a contemptible or incompetent person.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>weekend</word>
    <defn>The break in the working week, usually two days including the traditional holy or sabbath day. Thus in western countries, Saturday and Sunday.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>weekly</word>
    <defn>A publication that is published once a week.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>whenever</word>
    <defn>(interrogative) When ever: emphatic form of when.</defn>
    <defn>At any time.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>which</word>
    <defn>(interrogative) What one or ones (of those mentioned or implied).</defn>
    <defn>(relative) Introduces a relative clause giving further information about something previously mentioned.</defn>
    <defn>(relative) Used of people (now generally who, whom or that).</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>why</word>
    <defn>Reason</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>wild</word>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>window</word>
    <defn>The inedible parts of a grain-producing plant.</defn>
    <defn>Straw or hay cut up fine for the food of cattle.</defn>
    <defn>Any excess or unwanted material, resource, or person; anything worthless.</defn>
    <defn>Light jesting talk; banter; raillery.</defn>
    <defn>Loose material, e.g. small strips of aluminum foil dropped from aircraft, intended to interfere with radar detection.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>winner</word>
    <defn>One who has won or often wins.</defn>
    <defn>A point or goal that wins a competition.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>with</word>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>witness</word>
    <defn>Attestation of a fact or event; testimony.</defn>
    <defn>One who sees or has personal knowledge of something.</defn>
    <defn>Someone called to give evidence in a court.</defn>
    <defn>Something that serves as evidence; a sign or token.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>workshop</word>
    <defn>A room, especially one which is not particularly large, used for manufacturing or other light industrial work.</defn>
    <defn>A brief, intensive course of education for a small group, emphasizing interaction and practical problem solving.</defn>
    <defn>An academic conference.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>writer</word>
    <defn>A person who writes, or produces literary work.</defn>
    <defn>Anything that writes or produces output.</defn>
    <defn>The seller of an option.</defn>
    <defn>A clerk of a certain rank in the service of the East India Company, who, after serving a certain number of years, became a factor.</defn>
    <defn>An ordinary legal practitioner in Scottish country towns.</defn>
    <defn>A petty officer in the United States navy who keeps the watch-muster and other books of the ship.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>year</word>
    <defn>(by extension) The time it takes for any astronomical object (such as a planet, dwarf planet, small Solar System body, or comet) in direct orbit around a star (such as the Sun) to make one revolution around the star.</defn>
    <defn>A level or grade in school or college.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>yell</word>
    <defn>A shout.</defn>
    <defn>A phrase to be shouted.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>yellow</word>
    <defn>The colour of gold, butter, or a lemon; the colour obtained by mixing green and red light, or by subtracting blue from white light.</defn>
    <defn>The intermediate light in a set of three traffic lights, the illumination of which indicates that drivers should stop short of the intersection if it is safe to do so.</defn>
    <defn>One of the colour balls used in snooker, with a value of 2 points.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>you</word>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>young</word>
    <defn>Young or immature offspring (especially of an animal).</defn>
    <defn>(possibly nonstandard) An individual offspring; a single recently born or hatched organism.</defn>
  </item>
  <item>
    <word>yours</word>
    <defn>That which belongs to you (singular); the possessive second-person singular pronoun used without a following noun.</defn>
    <defn>That which belongs to you (plural); the possessive second-person plural pronoun used without a following noun.</defn>
    <defn>Written at the end of a letter, before the signature.</defn>
  </item>
</root>
